"[""Millsap's Double-Double Leads Hawks Over Grizzlies, 116-101"", [(u""Millsap's"", u'O'), (u'Double-Double', u'O'), (u'Leads', u'O'), (u'Hawks', u'O'), (u'Over', u'O'), (u'Grizzlies,', u'O'), (u'116-101', u'O')]]"
"['U.S. Citizens Might Be Present at Mali Hotel: State Department', [(u'U.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Citizens', u'O'), (u'Might', u'O'), (u'Be', u'O'), (u'Present', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Mali', u'LOCATION'), (u'Hotel:', u'O'), (u'State', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Department', u'ORGANIZATION')]]"
"['China to Restructure Poorly Performing State Firms-Assets Supervisor', [(u'China', u'LOCATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Restructure', u'O'), (u'Poorly', u'O'), (u'Performing', u'O'), (u'State', u'O'), (u'Firms-Assets', u'O'), (u'Supervisor', u'O')]]"
"['High-Profile Chinese Investor Xu Xiang Detained', [(u'High-Profile', u'O'), (u'Chinese', u'O'), (u'Investor', u'O'), (u'Xu', u'O'), (u'Xiang', u'O'), (u'Detained', u'O')]]"
"['Molly McCormick and Mark Street: Did Someone Play \xe2\x80\x98Come Fly With Me\xe2\x80\x99?', [(u'Molly', u'PERSON'), (u'McCormick', u'PERSON'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Mark', u'PERSON'), (u'Street:', u'O'), (u'Did', u'O'), (u'Someone', u'O'), (u'Play', u'O'), (u'‘Come', u'O'), (u'Fly', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Me’?', u'O')]]"
"['&#8216;Crescent to Cross&#8217; by Richard Long Is at Sperone Westwater', [(u'&#8216;Crescent', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Cross&#8217;', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Richard', u'PERSON'), (u'Long', u'PERSON'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Sperone', u'LOCATION'), (u'Westwater', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Republican Gov. Phil Bryant Wins Second Term in Mississippi', [(u'Republican', u'O'), (u'Gov.', u'O'), (u'Phil', u'PERSON'), (u'Bryant', u'PERSON'), (u'Wins', u'O'), (u'Second', u'O'), (u'Term', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Mississippi', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Illinois: Attorney General Seeks Release of a Police Video ', [(u'Illinois:', u'O'), (u'Attorney', u'O'), (u'General', u'O'), (u'Seeks', u'O'), (u'Release', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Police', u'O'), (u'Video', u'O')]]"
"[""Egypt's Military Controlling Repatriation of Russian Passengers: Russian Deputy PM"", [(u""Egypt's"", u'O'), (u'Military', u'O'), (u'Controlling', u'O'), (u'Repatriation', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Russian', u'O'), (u'Passengers:', u'O'), (u'Russian', u'O'), (u'Deputy', u'O'), (u'PM', u'O')]]"
"['High School Player Dies', [(u'High', u'O'), (u'School', u'O'), (u'Player', u'O'), (u'Dies', u'O')]]"
"[""Jets' Maccagnan Goes From Behind Scenes to Sudden Celebrity"", [(u""Jets'"", u'O'), (u'Maccagnan', u'O'), (u'Goes', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'Behind', u'O'), (u'Scenes', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Sudden', u'O'), (u'Celebrity', u'O')]]"
"['Detective Shoots Man Who Tried to Rob Officers in Brooklyn, Police Say', [(u'Detective', u'O'), (u'Shoots', u'O'), (u'Man', u'O'), (u'Who', u'O'), (u'Tried', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Rob', u'O'), (u'Officers', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Brooklyn,', u'O'), (u'Police', u'O'), (u'Say', u'O')]]"
"['A World War I Memorial in Kansas City Is a Tribute to Giving', [(u'A', u'O'), (u'World', u'O'), (u'War', u'O'), (u'I', u'O'), (u'Memorial', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Kansas', u'LOCATION'), (u'City', u'LOCATION'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Tribute', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Giving', u'O')]]"
"['Baku Thinks Big and Small for F1 Debut', [(u'Baku', u'LOCATION'), (u'Thinks', u'O'), (u'Big', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Small', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'F1', u'O'), (u'Debut', u'O')]]"
"['Restoring a Temple of Love as a Yonkers Eden Is Revived', [(u'Restoring', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Temple', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Love', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Yonkers', u'O'), (u'Eden', u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'Revived', u'O')]]"
"[""Palestinian 'Day of Rage' claims victims"", [(u'Palestinian', u'O'), (u""'Day"", u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u""Rage'"", u'O'), (u'claims', u'O'), (u'victims', u'O')]]"
"['Watches that Take the Plunge', [(u'Watches', u'O'), (u'that', u'O'), (u'Take', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Plunge', u'O')]]"
"['The Latest: Prosecutors: Man Eyed Targets After Brother Shot', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Latest:', u'O'), (u'Prosecutors:', u'O'), (u'Man', u'O'), (u'Eyed', u'O'), (u'Targets', u'O'), (u'After', u'O'), (u'Brother', u'O'), (u'Shot', u'O')]]"
"['Part Exhibitionism, Part Surveillance', [(u'Part', u'O'), (u'Exhibitionism,', u'O'), (u'Part', u'O'), (u'Surveillance', u'O')]]"
"['Second Win for Sunderland', [(u'Second', u'O'), (u'Win', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Sunderland', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Migrants Cling to Hungarian Train West, Lawmakers Debate Sealing Border', [(u'Migrants', u'O'), (u'Cling', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Hungarian', u'O'), (u'Train', u'O'), (u'West,', u'O'), (u'Lawmakers', u'O'), (u'Debate', u'O'), (u'Sealing', u'O'), (u'Border', u'O')]]"
"['Amy Winehouse Documentary Team Tackling Oasis in Upcoming Film', [(u'Amy', u'PERSON'), (u'Winehouse', u'PERSON'), (u'Documentary', u'O'), (u'Team', u'O'), (u'Tackling', u'O'), (u'Oasis', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Upcoming', u'O'), (u'Film', u'O')]]"
"['In Uganda, Pope Honors Christian Martyrs, Meets Youth', [(u'In', u'O'), (u'Uganda,', u'O'), (u'Pope', u'O'), (u'Honors', u'O'), (u'Christian', u'O'), (u'Martyrs,', u'O'), (u'Meets', u'O'), (u'Youth', u'O')]]"
"['Abid Naseer Receives 40-Year Sentence for Bomb Plot', [(u'Abid', u'PERSON'), (u'Naseer', u'PERSON'), (u'Receives', u'O'), (u'40-Year', u'O'), (u'Sentence', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Bomb', u'O'), (u'Plot', u'O')]]"
"['Staying in Afghanistan: The Ambassador\xe2\x80\x99s View', [(u'Staying', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Afghanistan:', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Ambassador’s', u'O'), (u'View', u'O')]]"
"['Judge Hears Arguments on Fantasy Sports', [(u'Judge', u'O'), (u'Hears', u'O'), (u'Arguments', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Fantasy', u'O'), (u'Sports', u'O')]]"
"['Ellen DeGeneres Interview Offers Hillary Clinton Chance to Connect With Women', [(u'Ellen', u'PERSON'), (u'DeGeneres', u'PERSON'), (u'Interview', u'O'), (u'Offers', u'O'), (u'Hillary', u'PERSON'), (u'Clinton', u'PERSON'), (u'Chance', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Connect', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Women', u'O')]]"
"[""Royals' Orlando Becomes First Brazilian in World Series"", [(u""Royals'"", u'O'), (u'Orlando', u'LOCATION'), (u'Becomes', u'O'), (u'First', u'O'), (u'Brazilian', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'World', u'O'), (u'Series', u'O')]]"
"['The Latest: 2 Victims Stabbed Inside Classroom, 2 Outdoors', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Latest:', u'O'), (u'2', u'O'), (u'Victims', u'O'), (u'Stabbed', u'O'), (u'Inside', u'O'), (u'Classroom,', u'O'), (u'2', u'O'), (u'Outdoors', u'O')]]"
"['Apple Beats Earnings Estimates, Issues Healthy Forecast', [(u'Apple', u'O'), (u'Beats', u'O'), (u'Earnings', u'O'), (u'Estimates,', u'O'), (u'Issues', u'O'), (u'Healthy', u'O'), (u'Forecast', u'O')]]"
"['E.C.B. Expected to Expand Stimulus, as Questions of Effects Remain', [(u'E.C.B.', u'O'), (u'Expected', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Expand', u'O'), (u'Stimulus,', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Questions', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Effects', u'O'), (u'Remain', u'O')]]"
"['Theft of a Boxer\xe2\x80\x99s Championship Belts Devastates His Upstate Hometown', [(u'Theft', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Boxer’s', u'O'), (u'Championship', u'O'), (u'Belts', u'O'), (u'Devastates', u'O'), (u'His', u'O'), (u'Upstate', u'O'), (u'Hometown', u'O')]]"
"['Iraq says its forces advance towards Ramadi', [(u'Iraq', u'LOCATION'), (u'says', u'O'), (u'its', u'O'), (u'forces', u'O'), (u'advance', u'O'), (u'towards', u'O'), (u'Ramadi', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Tracey Stewart\xe2\x80\x99s Animal Planet', [(u'Tracey', u'PERSON'), (u'Stewart’s', u'O'), (u'Animal', u'O'), (u'Planet', u'O')]]"
"['River God, Drought Blamed for Power Shortages in Africa', [(u'River', u'O'), (u'God,', u'O'), (u'Drought', u'O'), (u'Blamed', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Power', u'O'), (u'Shortages', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Africa', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['After Missing Podium, Armstrong Must Reset Olympic Goals', [(u'After', u'O'), (u'Missing', u'O'), (u'Podium,', u'O'), (u'Armstrong', u'O'), (u'Must', u'O'), (u'Reset', u'O'), (u'Olympic', u'O'), (u'Goals', u'O')]]"
"['Date Night With the Democrats', [(u'Date', u'O'), (u'Night', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Democrats', u'O')]]"
"['Ferguson Announces Hiring of New City Manager', [(u'Ferguson', u'PERSON'), (u'Announces', u'O'), (u'Hiring', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'New', u'O'), (u'City', u'O'), (u'Manager', u'O')]]"
"['South Africa Boss Issues Rally Cry for Boks Amid Race Row', [(u'South', u'LOCATION'), (u'Africa', u'LOCATION'), (u'Boss', u'O'), (u'Issues', u'O'), (u'Rally', u'O'), (u'Cry', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Boks', u'O'), (u'Amid', u'O'), (u'Race', u'O'), (u'Row', u'O')]]"
"['Getting Names Wrong', [(u'Getting', u'O'), (u'Names', u'O'), (u'Wrong', u'O')]]"
"['Lawyers for Winston, Kinsman Unhappy on Eve of Documentary', [(u'Lawyers', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Winston,', u'O'), (u'Kinsman', u'O'), (u'Unhappy', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Eve', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Documentary', u'O')]]"
"['\xe2\x80\x98Paris\xe2\x80\x99 Is a Six-Part Mini-Series From France', [(u'‘Paris’', u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Six-Part', u'O'), (u'Mini-Series', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'France', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Rivals at Democratic Debate Attack Hillary Clinton', [(u'Rivals', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Democratic', u'O'), (u'Debate', u'O'), (u'Attack', u'O'), (u'Hillary', u'PERSON'), (u'Clinton', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Standing Still Not an Option for All Blacks', [(u'Standing', u'O'), (u'Still', u'O'), (u'Not', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'Option', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'All', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Blacks', u'ORGANIZATION')]]"
"['Central American Nation of Belize Holds Legislative Election', [(u'Central', u'O'), (u'American', u'O'), (u'Nation', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Belize', u'LOCATION'), (u'Holds', u'O'), (u'Legislative', u'O'), (u'Election', u'O')]]"
"['Evening Hours | A Monumental Celebration and More', [(u'Evening', u'O'), (u'Hours', u'O'), (u'|', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'Monumental', u'O'), (u'Celebration', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'More', u'O')]]"
"['New Dinosaur Species That Lived Above Arctic Circle Is Discovered', [(u'New', u'O'), (u'Dinosaur', u'O'), (u'Species', u'O'), (u'That', u'O'), (u'Lived', u'O'), (u'Above', u'O'), (u'Arctic', u'O'), (u'Circle', u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'Discovered', u'O')]]"
"['Coldplay Designs T-Shirts and More Shopping Events and Sales Happening in New York', [(u'Coldplay', u'O'), (u'Designs', u'O'), (u'T-Shirts', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'More', u'O'), (u'Shopping', u'O'), (u'Events', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Sales', u'O'), (u'Happening', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'New', u'LOCATION'), (u'York', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Two Palestinian Assailants Shot Dead in West Bank Stabbing Attempts: Israel', [(u'Two', u'O'), (u'Palestinian', u'O'), (u'Assailants', u'O'), (u'Shot', u'O'), (u'Dead', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'West', u'LOCATION'), (u'Bank', u'LOCATION'), (u'Stabbing', u'O'), (u'Attempts:', u'O'), (u'Israel', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['UNLV Hangs On for 72-69 Win Over No. 13 Indiana', [(u'UNLV', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Hangs', u'O'), (u'On', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'72-69', u'O'), (u'Win', u'O'), (u'Over', u'O'), (u'No.', u'O'), (u'13', u'O'), (u'Indiana', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Back to School With Thom Browne and Rodarte', [(u'Back', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'School', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Thom', u'PERSON'), (u'Browne', u'PERSON'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Rodarte', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Carson Defends Relationship With Dentist Convicted of Fraud', [(u'Carson', u'PERSON'), (u'Defends', u'O'), (u'Relationship', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Dentist', u'O'), (u'Convicted', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Fraud', u'O')]]"
"['Scope of National Security Inquiry Is Revealed ', [(u'Scope', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'National', u'O'), (u'Security', u'O'), (u'Inquiry', u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'Revealed', u'O')]]"
"['California Wildfire Evacuees Return Home, Find Charred Ruins', [(u'California', u'LOCATION'), (u'Wildfire', u'O'), (u'Evacuees', u'O'), (u'Return', u'O'), (u'Home,', u'O'), (u'Find', u'O'), (u'Charred', u'O'), (u'Ruins', u'O')]]"
"['Hispanics in Congress Ask Treasury to Prevent \xe2\x80\x98Catastrophe\xe2\x80\x99 in Puerto Rico', [(u'Hispanics', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Congress', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Ask', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Treasury', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Prevent', u'O'), (u'‘Catastrophe’', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Puerto', u'LOCATION'), (u'Rico', u'LOCATION')]]"
"[""With Climate at 'Breaking Point', Leaders Urge Breakthrough in Paris"", [(u'With', u'O'), (u'Climate', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u""'Breaking"", u'O'), (u""Point',"", u'O'), (u'Leaders', u'O'), (u'Urge', u'O'), (u'Breakthrough', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Paris', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['History Looms as World Cup Quarter-Finalists Fine-Tune', [(u'History', u'O'), (u'Looms', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'World', u'O'), (u'Cup', u'O'), (u'Quarter-Finalists', u'O'), (u'Fine-Tune', u'O')]]"
"['Review: The Weeknd Tiptoes Toward Intimacy, Then Retreats', [(u'Review:', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Weeknd', u'O'), (u'Tiptoes', u'O'), (u'Toward', u'O'), (u'Intimacy,', u'O'), (u'Then', u'O'), (u'Retreats', u'O')]]"
"['NATO Invites Montenegro to Join Alliance, Defying Russia', [(u'NATO', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Invites', u'O'), (u'Montenegro', u'LOCATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Join', u'O'), (u'Alliance,', u'O'), (u'Defying', u'O'), (u'Russia', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Elder Bush Says His Son Was Served Badly by Aides', [(u'Elder', u'O'), (u'Bush', u'PERSON'), (u'Says', u'O'), (u'His', u'O'), (u'Son', u'O'), (u'Was', u'O'), (u'Served', u'O'), (u'Badly', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Aides', u'O')]]"
"['Chlo\xc3\xab\xc2\xa0Sevigny\xe2\x80\x99s Wild Gucci Dress', [(u'Chlo\xeb', u'O'), (u'Sevigny’s', u'O'), (u'Wild', u'O'), (u'Gucci', u'O')]]"
"['Touch-Screen Counseling', [(u'Touch-Screen', u'O'), (u'Counseling', u'O')]]"
"['More Kids Kept Safe From Household Medicines, ER Trend Says', [(u'More', u'O'), (u'Kids', u'O'), (u'Kept', u'O'), (u'Safe', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'Household', u'O'), (u'Medicines,', u'O'), (u'ER', u'O'), (u'Trend', u'O'), (u'Says', u'O')]]"
"[""Deal Reached in Syria's Homs for Fighters to Leave"", [(u'Deal', u'O'), (u'Reached', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u""Syria's"", u'O'), (u'Homs', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Fighters', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Leave', u'O')]]"
"[""Students at Washington's Howard University Complain About Mold, Rats"", [(u'Students', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u""Washington's"", u'O'), (u'Howard', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'University', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Complain', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'About', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Mold,', u'O'), (u'Rats', u'O')]]"
"['In DC, Public Housing Tenants Forced Out, Then Homes Flipped', [(u'In', u'O'), (u'DC,', u'O'), (u'Public', u'O'), (u'Housing', u'O'), (u'Tenants', u'O'), (u'Forced', u'O'), (u'Out,', u'O'), (u'Then', u'O'), (u'Homes', u'O'), (u'Flipped', u'O')]]"
"['Givenchy\xe2\x80\x99s Bejeweled Masks and (Almost) Bare Faces', [(u'Givenchy’s', u'O'), (u'Bejeweled', u'O'), (u'Masks', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'(Almost)', u'O'), (u'Bare', u'O'), (u'Faces', u'O')]]"
"['Police: Man Threatened Students Learning to Parallel Park', [(u'Police:', u'O'), (u'Man', u'O'), (u'Threatened', u'O'), (u'Students', u'O'), (u'Learning', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Parallel', u'O'), (u'Park', u'O')]]"
"['Source: OPCW Believes Syrian Insurgents Used Mustard Gas', [(u'Source:', u'O'), (u'OPCW', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Believes', u'O'), (u'Syrian', u'O'), (u'Insurgents', u'O'), (u'Used', u'O'), (u'Mustard', u'O'), (u'Gas', u'O')]]"
"['Burkina Faso to Choose First New Leader in Three Decades', [(u'Burkina', u'PERSON'), (u'Faso', u'PERSON'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Choose', u'O'), (u'First', u'O'), (u'New', u'O'), (u'Leader', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Three', u'O'), (u'Decades', u'O')]]"
"['Fuel Shortages Reported in Rebel-Controlled Eastern Ukraine', [(u'Fuel', u'O'), (u'Shortages', u'O'), (u'Reported', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Rebel-Controlled', u'O'), (u'Eastern', u'O'), (u'Ukraine', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['11 Killed as Pakistanis Vote in Local Government Polls', [(u'11', u'O'), (u'Killed', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Pakistanis', u'O'), (u'Vote', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Local', u'O'), (u'Government', u'O'), (u'Polls', u'O')]]"
"['Rain Washes Out Third Straight Day in Bengaluru', [(u'Rain', u'O'), (u'Washes', u'O'), (u'Out', u'O'), (u'Third', u'O'), (u'Straight', u'O'), (u'Day', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Bengaluru', u'O')]]"
"['Woman Stops by Colorado Police Station to Hug Officer', [(u'Woman', u'O'), (u'Stops', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Colorado', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Police', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Station', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Hug', u'O'), (u'Officer', u'O')]]"
"[""Royals' Volquez to Start Possible Clincher After Dad's Death"", [(u""Royals'"", u'O'), (u'Volquez', u'PERSON'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Start', u'O'), (u'Possible', u'O'), (u'Clincher', u'O'), (u'After', u'O'), (u""Dad's"", u'O'), (u'Death', u'O')]]"
"['Leasing Begins for New York\xe2\x80\x99s First Micro-Apartments', [(u'Leasing', u'O'), (u'Begins', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'New', u'O'), (u'York’s', u'O'), (u'First', u'O'), (u'Micro-Apartments', u'O')]]"
"['Getting Hot and Heavy in the 1980s', [(u'Getting', u'O'), (u'Hot', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Heavy', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'1980s', u'O')]]"
"['Landmark Metro Theater in Manhattan Will Be Reborn as a Planet Fitness', [(u'Landmark', u'O'), (u'Metro', u'O'), (u'Theater', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Manhattan', u'LOCATION'), (u'Will', u'O'), (u'Be', u'O'), (u'Reborn', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Planet', u'O'), (u'Fitness', u'O')]]"
"['Chick-fil-A and the Politics of Eating', [(u'Chick-fil-A', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Politics', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Eating', u'O')]]"
"['$9.8 Billion Valuation for Ferrari', [(u'$9.8', u'O'), (u'Billion', u'O'), (u'Valuation', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Ferrari', u'ORGANIZATION')]]"
"['You Can&#8217;t Please Everyone', [(u'You', u'O'), (u'Can&#8217;t', u'O'), (u'Please', u'O'), (u'Everyone', u'O')]]"
"['Groupies, From Sex Symbols to Style Icons', [(u'Groupies,', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'Sex', u'O'), (u'Symbols', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Style', u'O'), (u'Icons', u'O')]]"
"['Truth and Lies: The Orwellian World of Politics', [(u'Truth', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Lies:', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Orwellian', u'O'), (u'World', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Politics', u'O')]]"
"['Recalling the Eloquent Loneliness of the Playwright Brian Friel', [(u'Recalling', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Eloquent', u'O'), (u'Loneliness', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Playwright', u'O'), (u'Brian', u'PERSON'), (u'Friel', u'PERSON')]]"
"['California Aid in Dying', [(u'California', u'LOCATION'), (u'Aid', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Dying', u'O')]]"
"['In Rachel Rossin\xe2\x80\x99s \xe2\x80\x98Lossy,\xe2\x80\x99 the Virtual Reality of Living in a Painting', [(u'In', u'O'), (u'Rachel', u'PERSON'), (u'Rossin’s', u'PERSON'), (u'‘Lossy,’', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Virtual', u'O'), (u'Reality', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Living', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Painting', u'O')]]"
"['Greece: Poll Shows Syriza Pulling Ahead in Election Run-Up', [(u'Greece:', u'O'), (u'Poll', u'O'), (u'Shows', u'O'), (u'Syriza', u'O'), (u'Pulling', u'O'), (u'Ahead', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Election', u'O'), (u'Run-Up', u'O')]]"
"['The Allure of the Unknown', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Allure', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Unknown', u'O')]]"
"['I Got a Mystery Tattoo From Scott Campbell', [(u'I', u'O'), (u'Got', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Mystery', u'O'), (u'Tattoo', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'Scott', u'PERSON'), (u'Campbell', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Reaction to Christmas Island Riots', [(u'Reaction', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Christmas', u'O'), (u'Island', u'O'), (u'Riots', u'O')]]"
"['Cassils: Transgender Artist Goes to Extremes', [(u'Cassils:', u'O'), (u'Transgender', u'O'), (u'Artist', u'O'), (u'Goes', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Extremes', u'O')]]"
"['Canada Pushes Back Deadline for Accepting 25,000 Syrian Refugees', [(u'Canada', u'LOCATION'), (u'Pushes', u'O'), (u'Back', u'O'), (u'Deadline', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Accepting', u'O'), (u'25,000', u'O'), (u'Syrian', u'O'), (u'Refugees', u'O')]]"
"['Tom Buckley, Versatile and Colorful Times Reporter, Dies at 87', [(u'Tom', u'PERSON'), (u'Buckley,', u'O'), (u'Versatile', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Colorful', u'O'), (u'Times', u'O'), (u'Reporter,', u'O'), (u'Dies', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'87', u'O')]]"
"['Iran Expects Nuclear Deal to Be Implemented in Early January', [(u'Iran', u'LOCATION'), (u'Expects', u'O'), (u'Nuclear', u'O'), (u'Deal', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Be', u'O'), (u'Implemented', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Early', u'O'), (u'January', u'O')]]"
"['Portugal Gets a New Government, but Probably Not for Long', [(u'Portugal', u'LOCATION'), (u'Gets', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'New', u'O'), (u'Government,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'Probably', u'O'), (u'Not', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Long', u'O')]]"
"['Schwartzel Leads by 3 Shots at Alfred Dunhill Championship', [(u'Schwartzel', u'PERSON'), (u'Leads', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'3', u'O'), (u'Shots', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Alfred', u'O'), (u'Dunhill', u'O'), (u'Championship', u'O')]]"
"['To Weld, Perchance, to Dream', [(u'To', u'O'), (u'Weld,', u'O'), (u'Perchance,', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Dream', u'O')]]"
"['Spooked by Sugar, Americans Search for Healthier Halloween Treats', [(u'Spooked', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Sugar,', u'O'), (u'Americans', u'O'), (u'Search', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Healthier', u'O'), (u'Halloween', u'O'), (u'Treats', u'O')]]"
"['Former Pro Wrestler Charged in Girlfriend\xe2\x80\x99s 1983 Death', [(u'Former', u'O'), (u'Pro', u'O'), (u'Wrestler', u'O'), (u'Charged', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Girlfriend’s', u'O'), (u'1983', u'O'), (u'Death', u'O')]]"
"['Review: Fall for Dance Opens With Miami Ballet and Che Malambo', [(u'Review:', u'O'), (u'Fall', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Dance', u'O'), (u'Opens', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Miami', u'LOCATION'), (u'Ballet', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Che', u'PERSON'), (u'Malambo', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Paid Notice: Deaths  GAYNOR, PHIL', [(u'Paid', u'O'), (u'Notice:', u'O'), (u'Deaths', u'O'), (u'GAYNOR,', u'O'), (u'PHIL', u'O')]]"
"[""Ronaldo and Messi Headline Ballon d'Or Shortlist"", [(u'Ronaldo', u'PERSON'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Messi', u'PERSON'), (u'Headline', u'PERSON'), (u'Ballon', u'PERSON'), (u""d'Or"", u'O'), (u'Shortlist', u'O')]]"
"['Presidential Candidates on Syrian No-Fly Zone', [(u'Presidential', u'O'), (u'Candidates', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Syrian', u'O'), (u'No-Fly', u'O'), (u'Zone', u'O')]]"
"['Is Cultural Appropriation Always Wrong?', [(u'Is', u'O'), (u'Cultural', u'O'), (u'Appropriation', u'O'), (u'Always', u'O'), (u'Wrong?', u'O')]]"
"['How to Win the Broadway Ticket Lottery ', [(u'How', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Win', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Broadway', u'O'), (u'Ticket', u'O'), (u'Lottery', u'O')]]"
"['\xe2\x80\x98Unforgettable,\xe2\x80\x99 Apparently Forever', [(u'‘Unforgettable,’', u'O'), (u'Apparently', u'O'), (u'Forever', u'O')]]"
"['\xe2\x80\x98The Song Machine,\xe2\x80\x99 by John Seabrook', [(u'‘The', u'O'), (u'Song', u'O'), (u'Machine,’', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'John', u'PERSON'), (u'Seabrook', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Homegrown pharma push to boost Chinese drugmakers', [(u'Homegrown', u'O'), (u'pharma', u'O'), (u'push', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'boost', u'O'), (u'Chinese', u'O'), (u'drugmakers', u'O')]]"
"['Oregon governor says community college shooter is deceased', [(u'Oregon', u'LOCATION'), (u'governor', u'O'), (u'says', u'O'), (u'community', u'O'), (u'college', u'O'), (u'shooter', u'O'), (u'is', u'O'), (u'deceased', u'O')]]"
"['Ask a Show Runner: Submit Questions for Sarah Treem of \xe2\x80\x98The Affair\xe2\x80\x99', [(u'Ask', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Show', u'O'), (u'Runner:', u'O'), (u'Submit', u'O'), (u'Questions', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Sarah', u'PERSON'), (u'Treem', u'PERSON'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'‘The', u'O'), (u'Affair’', u'O')]]"
"['Sam Raimi&#8217;s Evil Dead Rise Again on Television', [(u'Sam', u'PERSON'), (u'Raimi&#8217;s', u'O'), (u'Evil', u'O'), (u'Dead', u'O'), (u'Rise', u'O'), (u'Again', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Television', u'O')]]"
"['A Slice of Kreuzberg in an East Village Bar', [(u'A', u'O'), (u'Slice', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Kreuzberg', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'East', u'O'), (u'Village', u'O'), (u'Bar', u'O')]]"
"['Bill Gates Expected to Create Billion-Dollar Fund for Clean Energy', [(u'Bill', u'O'), (u'Gates', u'O'), (u'Expected', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Create', u'O'), (u'Billion-Dollar', u'O'), (u'Fund', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Clean', u'O'), (u'Energy', u'O')]]"
"['Universal Theme Parks Record Highest Summer Attendance', [(u'Universal', u'O'), (u'Theme', u'O'), (u'Parks', u'O'), (u'Record', u'O'), (u'Highest', u'O'), (u'Summer', u'O'), (u'Attendance', u'O')]]"
"['Air France Officials Swarmed by Workers', [(u'Air', u'O'), (u'France', u'O'), (u'Officials', u'O'), (u'Swarmed', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Workers', u'O')]]"
"['\xe2\x80\x98The Evolution of Everything,\xe2\x80\x99 by Matt Ridley', [(u'‘The', u'O'), (u'Evolution', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Everything,’', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Matt', u'PERSON'), (u'Ridley', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Pope Hints Central African Republic Visit Could Be Canceled', [(u'Pope', u'O'), (u'Hints', u'O'), (u'Central', u'O'), (u'African', u'O'), (u'Republic', u'O'), (u'Visit', u'O'), (u'Could', u'O'), (u'Be', u'O'), (u'Canceled', u'O')]]"
"['Janet Jackson, Shy Pop Star', [(u'Janet', u'O'), (u'Jackson,', u'O'), (u'Shy', u'O'), (u'Pop', u'O'), (u'Star', u'O')]]"
"['Euro Slightly Weaker in Early Trading Against Dollar', [(u'Euro', u'O'), (u'Slightly', u'O'), (u'Weaker', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Early', u'O'), (u'Trading', u'O'), (u'Against', u'O'), (u'Dollar', u'O')]]"
"[""Atlanta Fed's Lockhart Says Rate Case 'Compelling' Ahead of Last Review"", [(u'Atlanta', u'LOCATION'), (u""Fed's"", u'O'), (u'Lockhart', u'O'), (u'Says', u'O'), (u'Rate', u'O'), (u'Case', u'O'), (u""'Compelling'"", u'O'), (u'Ahead', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Last', u'O'), (u'Review', u'O')]]"
"['Mali Attack Weighing on Airline Stocks-Traders', [(u'Mali', u'LOCATION'), (u'Attack', u'O'), (u'Weighing', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Airline', u'O'), (u'Stocks-Traders', u'O')]]"
"['The Great British Immigration Debate', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Great', u'O'), (u'British', u'O'), (u'Immigration', u'O'), (u'Debate', u'O')]]"
"[""Egypt's Lost Queen Nefertiti May Lie Concealed in King Tut's Tomb"", [(u""Egypt's"", u'O'), (u'Lost', u'O'), (u'Queen', u'O'), (u'Nefertiti', u'PERSON'), (u'May', u'O'), (u'Lie', u'O'), (u'Concealed', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'King', u'O'), (u""Tut's"", u'O'), (u'Tomb', u'O')]]"
"['U.S. Store Sales Down Slightly for Thanksgiving and Black Friday', [(u'U.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Store', u'O'), (u'Sales', u'O'), (u'Down', u'O'), (u'Slightly', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Thanksgiving', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Black', u'O'), (u'Friday', u'O')]]"
"['Pope blesses sick, celebrates Mass in Uganda', [(u'Pope', u'O'), (u'blesses', u'O'), (u'sick,', u'O'), (u'celebrates', u'O'), (u'Mass', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Uganda', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Mother Who Locked Girl in Closet Found Guilty of Child Abuse', [(u'Mother', u'O'), (u'Who', u'O'), (u'Locked', u'O'), (u'Girl', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Closet', u'O'), (u'Found', u'O'), (u'Guilty', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Child', u'O'), (u'Abuse', u'O')]]"
"['Drugmakers Pfizer, Allergan Considering a Combination: WSJ', [(u'Drugmakers', u'O'), (u'Pfizer,', u'O'), (u'Allergan', u'O'), (u'Considering', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Combination:', u'O'), (u'WSJ', u'O')]]"
"['Dutch Report on Malaysia Flight 17', [(u'Dutch', u'O'), (u'Report', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Malaysia', u'LOCATION'), (u'Flight', u'O'), (u'17', u'O')]]"
"['Recasting Rodin\xe2\x80\x99s Life and Work', [(u'Recasting', u'O'), (u'Rodin’s', u'O'), (u'Life', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Work', u'O')]]"
"['From Barbara Taylor Bradford: A Life Story That Dazzles', [(u'From', u'O'), (u'Barbara', u'PERSON'), (u'Taylor', u'PERSON'), (u'Bradford:', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'Life', u'O'), (u'Story', u'O'), (u'That', u'O'), (u'Dazzles', u'O')]]"
"['Gordon Takes Pole', [(u'Gordon', u'PERSON'), (u'Takes', u'O'), (u'Pole', u'O')]]"
"['Diverse Paris Mourns Together After Indiscriminate Violence', [(u'Diverse', u'O'), (u'Paris', u'LOCATION'), (u'Mourns', u'O'), (u'Together', u'O'), (u'After', u'O'), (u'Indiscriminate', u'O'), (u'Violence', u'O')]]"
"['Cindy Holland of Netflix: Learning to Lead on a Pair of Water Skis', [(u'Cindy', u'PERSON'), (u'Holland', u'PERSON'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Netflix:', u'O'), (u'Learning', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Lead', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Pair', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Water', u'O'), (u'Skis', u'O')]]"
"['Connor McDavid Excited About Making NHL Debut', [(u'Connor', u'PERSON'), (u'McDavid', u'PERSON'), (u'Excited', u'O'), (u'About', u'O'), (u'Making', u'O'), (u'NHL', u'O'), (u'Debut', u'O')]]"
"['Asian-Americans and Stereotypes', [(u'Asian-Americans', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Stereotypes', u'O')]]"
"['Fox, SiriusXM Launch Headline News Service', [(u'Fox,', u'O'), (u'SiriusXM', u'O'), (u'Launch', u'O'), (u'Headline', u'O'), (u'News', u'O'), (u'Service', u'O')]]"
"['In Religious Arbitration, Scripture Is the Rule of Law', [(u'In', u'O'), (u'Religious', u'O'), (u'Arbitration,', u'O'), (u'Scripture', u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Rule', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Law', u'O')]]"
"['Review: At Fall for Dance Festival, Female Power', [(u'Review:', u'O'), (u'At', u'O'), (u'Fall', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Dance', u'O'), (u'Festival,', u'O'), (u'Female', u'O'), (u'Power', u'O')]]"
"[""Koscielny 'Deeply Affected' by Paris Attacks, Says Wenger"", [(u'Koscielny', u'PERSON'), (u""'Deeply"", u'O'), (u""Affected'"", u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'Paris', u'LOCATION'), (u'Attacks,', u'O'), (u'Says', u'O'), (u'Wenger', u'PERSON')]]"
"['ACLU, CAIR, Muslim Inmates Sue Over Miami-Dade Jail Meals', [(u'ACLU,', u'O'), (u'CAIR,', u'O'), (u'Muslim', u'O'), (u'Inmates', u'O'), (u'Sue', u'O'), (u'Over', u'O'), (u'Miami-Dade', u'O'), (u'Jail', u'O'), (u'Meals', u'O')]]"
"['Salt and Pepper Roast Chicken', [(u'Salt', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Pepper', u'O'), (u'Roast', u'O'), (u'Chicken', u'O')]]"
"['The Grown-Ups Take the Stage at the Democratic Debate', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Grown-Ups', u'O'), (u'Take', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Stage', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Democratic', u'O'), (u'Debate', u'O')]]"
"['Baltimore Police Assailed for Response After Freddie Gray\xe2\x80\x99s Death', [(u'Baltimore', u'LOCATION'), (u'Police', u'O'), (u'Assailed', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Response', u'O'), (u'After', u'O'), (u'Freddie', u'O'), (u'Gray’s', u'O'), (u'Death', u'O')]]"
"['Report: Plane Likely Overweight in Crash That Killed 4', [(u'Report:', u'O'), (u'Plane', u'O'), (u'Likely', u'O'), (u'Overweight', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Crash', u'O'), (u'That', u'O'), (u'Killed', u'O'), (u'4', u'O')]]"
"['Obama Heads to a Crowded Iowa, but Will Stay Off the Trail', [(u'Obama', u'PERSON'), (u'Heads', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Crowded', u'O'), (u'Iowa,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'Will', u'O'), (u'Stay', u'O'), (u'Off', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Trail', u'O')]]"
"['Zafgen Reports Second Death in Key Drug Study', [(u'Zafgen', u'O'), (u'Reports', u'O'), (u'Second', u'O'), (u'Death', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Key', u'O'), (u'Drug', u'O'), (u'Study', u'O')]]"
"['Cisse Keen to Win Back Starting Place at Newcastle', [(u'Cisse', u'O'), (u'Keen', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Win', u'O'), (u'Back', u'O'), (u'Starting', u'O'), (u'Place', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Newcastle', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['World\xe2\x80\x99s Biggest Animal Cloning Center Set for \xe2\x80\x9916 in a Skeptical China', [(u'World’s', u'O'), (u'Biggest', u'O'), (u'Animal', u'O'), (u'Cloning', u'O'), (u'Center', u'O'), (u'Set', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'’16', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Skeptical', u'O'), (u'China', u'LOCATION')]]"
"[""New York Man Creates 'Sovereign Nation' in Utah"", [(u'New', u'LOCATION'), (u'York', u'LOCATION'), (u'Man', u'O'), (u'Creates', u'O'), (u""'Sovereign"", u'O'), (u""Nation'"", u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Utah', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Channel Tunnel Migrant Emerges at Center of Asylum Debate', [(u'Channel', u'O'), (u'Tunnel', u'O'), (u'Migrant', u'O'), (u'Emerges', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Center', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Asylum', u'O'), (u'Debate', u'O')]]"
"['When Buying Gift Cards, Know Your Audience (and Their Age)', [(u'When', u'O'), (u'Buying', u'O'), (u'Gift', u'O'), (u'Cards,', u'O'), (u'Know', u'O'), (u'Your', u'O'), (u'Audience', u'O'), (u'(and', u'O'), (u'Their', u'O'), (u'Age)', u'O')]]"
"['German Prosecutors Charge Suspected Islamist for Preparing Bombing', [(u'German', u'O'), (u'Prosecutors', u'O'), (u'Charge', u'O'), (u'Suspected', u'O'), (u'Islamist', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Preparing', u'O'), (u'Bombing', u'O')]]"
"[""Republicans Want Tougher Response to ISIS 'War'"", [(u'Republicans', u'O'), (u'Want', u'O'), (u'Tougher', u'O'), (u'Response', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'ISIS', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u""'War'"", u'O')]]"
"['U.S. Senators Call for 20,000 Troops in Syria and Iraq', [(u'U.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Senators', u'O'), (u'Call', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'20,000', u'O'), (u'Troops', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Syria', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Iraq', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['The Latest: Illinois Attorney General Asks for Federal Probe', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Latest:', u'O'), (u'Illinois', u'LOCATION'), (u'Attorney', u'O'), (u'General', u'O'), (u'Asks', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Federal', u'O'), (u'Probe', u'O')]]"
"['Corporation to Oversee New Hudson Rail Tunnel, With U.S. and Amtrak Financing Half', [(u'Corporation', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Oversee', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'New', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Hudson', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Rail', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Tunnel,', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'U.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Amtrak', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Financing', u'O'), (u'Half', u'O')]]"
"['The Real Problem With the Economy', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Real', u'O'), (u'Problem', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Economy', u'O')]]"
"['Review: Michel Houellebecq\xe2\x80\x99s \xe2\x80\x98Submission\xe2\x80\x99 Imagines France as a Muslim State', [(u'Review:', u'O'), (u'Michel', u'PERSON'), (u'Houellebecq’s', u'PERSON'), (u'‘Submission’', u'O'), (u'Imagines', u'O'), (u'France', u'LOCATION'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Muslim', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'State', u'ORGANIZATION')]]"
"['Paid Notice: Memorials  BRODMAN, DR. L. ELIZABETH B. NOVEMBER 23, 1918, OCTOBER 19, 2015. ADORED MOTHER, SPOUSE AND SISTER, COMPASSIONATE AND GROUND BREAKING PHYSICIAN, DIED AT HOME IN STAMFORD, CONNECTICUT, EARLY IN THE MORNING ON OCTOBER 19, 2015, HAVING GRACEFULLY WITNESSED THE WORST AND EXEMPLIFIED THE BEST CHANGES IN AMERICA IN THE LAST ONE HUNDRED YEARS. NAMED AFTER HER ANCESTORS, SHE WAS BORN LILLE ELIZABETH BEEKLEY ON NOVEMBER 23, 1918, TWO YEARS BEFORE WOMEN GOT THE RIGHT TO VOTE, ON A FARM IN GLENDALE, OHIO, TO A FAMILY THAT TRACES ITS HISTORY TO THE SETTLEMENT OF GREENWICH, CONNECTICUT IN 1640, AND PARTICIPATED IN THE AMERICAN REVOLUTION. SHE WAS THE COURAGEOUS OLDEST OF FIVE SISTERS. WHEN ELIZABETH WAS JUST SEVEN YEARS OLD, HER MOTHER DIED OF PNEUMONIA. UNABLE TO CARE FOR ALL FIVE SIBLINGS, THEIR FATHER PLACED ELIZABETH AND NEXT OLDEST, RUTH, IN BETHANY HOME, RUN BY THE EPISCOPAL SISTERS. EVENTUALLY, BY HIGH SCHOOL, BOTH GIRLS RETURNED TO LIVE WITH THEIR FATHER AND ADORED PATERNAL GRANDMOTHER, HER GRAMMAR, WITH WHOM ELIZABETH SHARED A BED. AT GLENDALE HIGH SCHOOL, EVER FOCUSED AND SELF, DEFINED, ELIZABETH TOOK UP THE TROMBONE AND ALSO PLAYED ON THE BASKETBALL TEAM. SHE GRADUATED HIGH SCHOOL IN A CLASS OF SIXTEEN STUDENTS. IN THE LATE 1930S, ELIZABETH ENTERED MIAMI UNIVERSITY IN OHIO, ARRIVING WITH A WARDROBE SHE HAD SEWN HERSELF. SHE GRADUATED FROM COLLEGE WITH HONORS IN BIOLOGY. SHE THEN ATTENDED THE UNIVERSITY OF CINCINNATI SCHOOL OF MEDICINE WHERE SHE WORKED AT NIGHT AS A LABORATORY TECHNICIAN. SHE WAS ONE OF TWO WOMEN IN HER 1945 GRADUATING CLASS OF 86. DURING HER CLINICAL YEARS IN MEDICAL SCHOOL, WHEN THE CLASS WAS DIVIDED BETWEEN MEDICINE AND SURGERY, SHE PITCHED IN THE SOFTBALL GAMES. THE YEAR ELIZABETH GRADUATED MEDICAL SCHOOL WAS THE FIRST YEAR HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL ADMITTED WOMEN. HAD SHE NOT MET AND MARRIED HER FUTURE HUSBAND IN MEDICAL SCHOOL, DR. HAROLD BRODMAN, WHO PURSUED HER WITH ZEAL, ELIZABETH LIKELY WOULD HAVE SPENT LIFE AS A DOCTOR HELPING CHILDREN IN THE 3RD WORLD. INSTEAD, SHE BEGAN HER MEDICAL PRACTICE AND BECAME A MOTHER ALL AT ONCE. THERE IS A LOVELY PHOTOGRAPH DOCUMENTING THIS TIME, OF ELIZABETH IN CAP AND BURSTING GOWN, EVIDENCING HER JOY. SOON AFTER THE PHOTO WAS TAKEN, ELIZABETH, JUST SIX AND ONE HALF MONTHS PREGNANT WITH TWIN BOYS, WENT INTO PRECIPITOUS LABOR; IT WAS THE LAST DAY OF HER STATE BOARD EXAMINATIONS. BUT WITH THE SEEMING EASE AND DETERMINATION SHE SHOWED THROUGHOUT HER LIFE, ELIZABETH COMPLETED THE EXAM AND THEN WENT TO ST. FRANCIS HOSPITAL IN COLUMBUS, WHERE HER SONS CHARLES AND RICHARD WERE BORN. EIGHT YEARS LATER SHE GAVE BIRTH TO HER DAUGHTER, LOUISE. IN THOSE YEARS, DR. ELIZABETH BRODMAN CONTINUED WORK AS A PHYSICIAN, JUGGLING PARENTHOOD, ALWAYS FINDING TIME FOR HER CHILDREN. A TALENTED PAINTER, SHE ALSO FOUND TIME TO STUDY AT THE ARTS STUDENTS LEAGUE IN NEW YORK WITH REGINALD MARSH. THEN, WHEN HER SONS WENT OFF TO COLLEGE AND HER DAUGHTER WAS A BIT MORE INDEPENDENT, SHE TOOK A RESIDENCY IN ANESTHESIOLOGY AT ALBERT EINSTEIN COLLEGE OF MEDICINE AND FOLLOWING, CONTINUED WORK FULL TIME AS AN ATTENDING AND ASSOCIATE PROFESSOR AT ALBERT EINSTEIN COLLEGE OF MEDICINE. THERE, SHE CREATED THE PEDIATRIC ANESTHESIA SPECIALTY AND BECAME ASSISTANT PROFESSOR OF PEDIATRICS AND THE CLINICAL DIRECTOR OF THE DEPARTMENT OF ANESTHESIA. SHE WAS PERFECTLY SUITED FOR PEDIATRICS, SHE LOVED CHILDREN, WOULD COMPASSIONATELY READY HER YOUNG PATIENTS FOR SURGERY, AND COMFORTINGLY ALLAY THEIR FEARS. RETURNING IN LATER YEARS TO HER CORE DESIRE TO HELP THOSE WITHOUT RESOURCES, DR. BRODMAN VOLUNTEERED WITH HER HUSBAND TO WORK IN THIRD WORLD COUNTRIES, GIVING ANESTHESIA FOR THE NEEDY AND TEACHING FOREIGN PHYSICIANS IN THEIR OWN LANDS, USING MATERIALS AVAILABLE THERE TO TEACH NEW TECHNIQUES. IN 1972 SHE WORKED AT THE AVICENNA HOSPITAL IN KABUL, AFGHANISTAN; IN 1975 IN SURAKARTA AND MALANG, JAVA; IN 1991 IN HANGCHOU, CHINA AND IN 1992 AT THE LUTHERAN HOSPITAL ON THE WEST BANK IN ISRAEL. IN AFGHANISTAN DR. BRODMAN EXECUTED AND TAUGHT THE CENTRAL VENOUS MONITORING TECHNIQUE, THE FIRST SUCH PROCEDURE IN CENTRAL ASIA. IN CHINA AND ISRAEL SHE WAS ESPECIALLY FOND OF THE WORK, CORRECTING FACIAL DEFORMITIES OF CHILDREN TO GIVE THEM A NEW CHANCE IN LIFE. IN 1995 AT HER 50TH MEDICAL SCHOOL REUNION, DR. BRODMAN WAS GIVEN THE DISTINGUISHED ALUMNI AWARD FOR THE CLASS OF 1945. DR. BRODMAN WAS A RESPECTED MEMBER OF THE AMERICAN SOCIETY OF ANESTHESIOLOGISTS, THE NEW YORK STATE SOCIETY OF ANESTHESIOLOGISTS AND THE INTERNATIONAL ANESTHESIA RESEARCH SOCIETY. IN ADDITION, SHE AUTHORED AND CO, AUTHORED NUMEROUS COMMUNICATIONS IN REVIEWED JOURNALS AS WELL AS SEVERAL BOOKS, BOOK CHAPTERS, REVIEW ARTICLES AND ABSTRACTS. DR. BRODMAN RETIRED FROM MEDICINE AT AGE 76, AS SHE SAID, ""BEFORE SHE MADE ANY MISTAKES."" SHE WOULD HAVE LIKED TO HAVE DIED WITH HER BOOTS ON, PRACTICING MEDICINE. NEVER LIKING TO BE INACTIVE, SHE RETURNED AFTER RETIRING FROM MEDICINE TO STUDYING PAINTING WITH THE ARTS STUDENTS LEAGUE AT THE VYTLACIL CAMPUS IN SPARKILL, NY. ALWAYS A DEEP SORROW, ELIZABETH WAS PREDECEASED BY HER SON CHARLES IN 1977 WHEN HE WAS 31, A HEART BREAKING LOSS FOR THE FAMILY WHICH ELIZABETH HELD TOGETHER WITH NOTHING SHORT OF GRACE, LOVE, AND HER ASTONISHING STRENGTH OF WILL. A YEAR LATER, ELIZABETH SUFFERED ANOTHER TERRIBLE LOSS, HER GREATEST CONFIDANT AND FRIEND, HER SISTER MIDGE, DIED IN A CAR ACCIDENT. AGAIN ELIZABETH DID NOT LET LOSS, THOUGH EVER PRESENT, DEFINE HER; SHE QUIETLY, COMPASSIONATELY, AND LOVINGLY PERSEVERED. ELIZABETH B. BRODMAN IS SURVIVED BY HER DEVOTED AND ADORING FAMILY: HER HUSBAND OF ALMOST 72 YEARS, DR. HAROLD BRODMAN, A GENERAL SURGEON, HER SON DR. RICHARD BRODMAN, A CARDIOTHORACIC SURGEON, HER DAUGHTER, LOUISE, AN ARCHITECT, HER GRANDDAUGHTER, ALEXANDRA, A NASSAU COUNTY ASSISTANT DISTRICT ATTORNEY, AND THEIR SPOUSES, AS WELL AS HERO AND HARLEY, POODLES WHO BROUGHT SOME LIGHT HEARTED PLAY TO ELIZABETH IN HER LAST YEARS. THE MOST GENEROUS OF SOULS, AN ENVIRONMENTALIST BEFORE THE WORD BECAME KNOWN, A COURAGEOUS AND FUN LOVING ADVENTURER WHO CANOED WHITE WATER AND TRAVELED THE WORLD WITH THE DESIRE TO HELP OTHERS, A PAINTER WHO LOVED THE BEAUTY OF THE NATURAL WORLD AS WELL AS THE WONDERS OF SCIENTISTS AND ARTISTS, A LOVING MOTHER AND SPOUSE, ELIZABETH MADE EVERYONE BETTER FOR HAVING KNOWN HER. DESPITE THE SORROWS SHE SUFFERED OVER HER REMARKABLE LIFE, SHE MADE EVERYTHING SEEM EFFORTLESS, AND JOYFUL. SHE LIVED BY HER OWN EXPECTATIONS AND INTERESTS. SHE LOVED AND WAS LOVED. 1', [(u'Paid', u'O'), (u'Notice:', u'O'), (u'Memorials', u'O'), (u'BRODMAN,', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'L.', u'PERSON'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'B.', u'PERSON'), (u'NOVEMBER', u'O'), (u'23,', u'O'), (u'1918,', u'O'), (u'OCTOBER', u'O'), (u'19,', u'O'), (u'2015.', u'O'), (u'ADORED', u'O'), (u'MOTHER,', u'O'), (u'SPOUSE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'SISTER,', u'O'), (u'COMPASSIONATE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'GROUND', u'O'), (u'BREAKING', u'O'), (u'PHYSICIAN,', u'O'), (u'DIED', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'HOME', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'STAMFORD,', u'O'), (u'CONNECTICUT,', u'O'), (u'EARLY', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'MORNING', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'OCTOBER', u'O'), (u'19,', u'O'), (u'2015,', u'O'), (u'HAVING', u'O'), (u'GRACEFULLY', u'O'), (u'WITNESSED', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'WORST', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'EXEMPLIFIED', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'BEST', u'O'), (u'CHANGES', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'AMERICA', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'LAST', u'O'), (u'ONE', u'O'), (u'HUNDRED', u'O'), (u'YEARS.', u'O'), (u'NAMED', u'O'), (u'AFTER', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'ANCESTORS,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'BORN', u'O'), (u'LILLE', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'BEEKLEY', u'PERSON'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'NOVEMBER', u'O'), (u'23,', u'O'), (u'1918,', u'O'), (u'TWO', u'O'), (u'YEARS', u'O'), (u'BEFORE', u'O'), (u'WOMEN', u'O'), (u'GOT', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'RIGHT', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'VOTE,', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'FARM', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'GLENDALE,', u'O'), (u'OHIO,', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'FAMILY', u'O'), (u'THAT', u'O'), (u'TRACES', u'O'), (u'ITS', u'O'), (u'HISTORY', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'SETTLEMENT', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'GREENWICH,', u'O'), (u'CONNECTICUT', u'LOCATION'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1640,', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'PARTICIPATED', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'AMERICAN', u'O'), (u'REVOLUTION.', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'COURAGEOUS', u'O'), (u'OLDEST', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'FIVE', u'O'), (u'SISTERS.', u'O'), (u'WHEN', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'JUST', u'O'), (u'SEVEN', u'O'), (u'YEARS', u'O'), (u'OLD,', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'MOTHER', u'O'), (u'DIED', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'PNEUMONIA.', u'O'), (u'UNABLE', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'CARE', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'ALL', u'O'), (u'FIVE', u'O'), (u'SIBLINGS,', u'O'), (u'THEIR', u'O'), (u'FATHER', u'O'), (u'PLACED', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'NEXT', u'O'), (u'OLDEST,', u'O'), (u'RUTH,', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'BETHANY', u'LOCATION'), (u'HOME,', u'O'), (u'RUN', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'EPISCOPAL', u'O'), (u'SISTERS.', u'O'), (u'EVENTUALLY,', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'HIGH', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL,', u'O'), (u'BOTH', u'O'), (u'GIRLS', u'O'), (u'RETURNED', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'LIVE', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'THEIR', u'O'), (u'FATHER', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ADORED', u'O'), (u'PATERNAL', u'O'), (u'GRANDMOTHER,', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'GRAMMAR,', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'WHOM', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'SHARED', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'BED.', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'GLENDALE', u'LOCATION'), (u'HIGH', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL,', u'O'), (u'EVER', u'O'), (u'FOCUSED', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'SELF,', u'O'), (u'DEFINED,', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'TOOK', u'O'), (u'UP', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'TROMBONE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ALSO', u'O'), (u'PLAYED', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'BASKETBALL', u'O'), (u'TEAM.', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'GRADUATED', u'O'), (u'HIGH', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'CLASS', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'SIXTEEN', u'O'), (u'STUDENTS.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'LATE', u'O'), (u'1930S,', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'ENTERED', u'O'), (u'MIAMI', u'O'), (u'UNIVERSITY', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'OHIO,', u'O'), (u'ARRIVING', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'WARDROBE', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'HAD', u'O'), (u'SEWN', u'O'), (u'HERSELF.', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'GRADUATED', u'O'), (u'FROM', u'O'), (u'COLLEGE', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'HONORS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'BIOLOGY.', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'THEN', u'O'), (u'ATTENDED', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'UNIVERSITY', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'CINCINNATI', u'LOCATION'), (u'SCHOOL', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'MEDICINE', u'O'), (u'WHERE', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'WORKED', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'NIGHT', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'LABORATORY', u'O'), (u'TECHNICIAN.', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'ONE', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'TWO', u'O'), (u'WOMEN', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'1945', u'O'), (u'GRADUATING', u'O'), (u'CLASS', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'86.', u'O'), (u'DURING', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'CLINICAL', u'O'), (u'YEARS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'MEDICAL', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL,', u'O'), (u'WHEN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'CLASS', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'DIVIDED', u'O'), (u'BETWEEN', u'O'), (u'MEDICINE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'SURGERY,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'PITCHED', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'SOFTBALL', u'O'), (u'GAMES.', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'YEAR', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'GRADUATED', u'O'), (u'MEDICAL', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'FIRST', u'O'), (u'YEAR', u'O'), (u'HARVARD', u'O'), (u'MEDICAL', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL', u'O'), (u'ADMITTED', u'O'), (u'WOMEN.', u'O'), (u'HAD', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'NOT', u'O'), (u'MET', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'MARRIED', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'FUTURE', u'O'), (u'HUSBAND', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'MEDICAL', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL,', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'HAROLD', u'PERSON'), (u'BRODMAN,', u'PERSON'), (u'WHO', u'O'), (u'PURSUED', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'ZEAL,', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'O'), (u'LIKELY', u'O'), (u'WOULD', u'O'), (u'HAVE', u'O'), (u'SPENT', u'O'), (u'LIFE', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'DOCTOR', u'O'), (u'HELPING', u'O'), (u'CHILDREN', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'3RD', u'O'), (u'WORLD.', u'O'), (u'INSTEAD,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'BEGAN', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'MEDICAL', u'O'), (u'PRACTICE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'BECAME', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'MOTHER', u'O'), (u'ALL', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'ONCE.', u'O'), (u'THERE', u'O'), (u'IS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'LOVELY', u'O'), (u'PHOTOGRAPH', u'O'), (u'DOCUMENTING', u'O'), (u'THIS', u'O'), (u'TIME,', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'CAP', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'BURSTING', u'O'), (u'GOWN,', u'O'), (u'EVIDENCING', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'JOY.', u'O'), (u'SOON', u'O'), (u'AFTER', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'PHOTO', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'TAKEN,', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH,', u'O'), (u'JUST', u'O'), (u'SIX', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ONE', u'O'), (u'HALF', u'O'), (u'MONTHS', u'O'), (u'PREGNANT', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'TWIN', u'O'), (u'BOYS,', u'O'), (u'WENT', u'O'), (u'INTO', u'O'), (u'PRECIPITOUS', u'O'), (u'LABOR;', u'O'), (u'IT', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'LAST', u'O'), (u'DAY', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'STATE', u'O'), (u'BOARD', u'O'), (u'EXAMINATIONS.', u'O'), (u'BUT', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'SEEMING', u'O'), (u'EASE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'DETERMINATION', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'SHOWED', u'O'), (u'THROUGHOUT', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'LIFE,', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'O'), (u'COMPLETED', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'EXAM', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'THEN', u'O'), (u'WENT', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'ST.', u'O'), (u'FRANCIS', u'O'), (u'HOSPITAL', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'COLUMBUS,', u'O'), (u'WHERE', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'SONS', u'O'), (u'CHARLES', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'RICHARD', u'O'), (u'WERE', u'O'), (u'BORN.', u'O'), (u'EIGHT', u'O'), (u'YEARS', u'O'), (u'LATER', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'GAVE', u'O'), (u'BIRTH', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'DAUGHTER,', u'O'), (u'LOUISE.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THOSE', u'O'), (u'YEARS,', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'BRODMAN', u'PERSON'), (u'CONTINUED', u'O'), (u'WORK', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'PHYSICIAN,', u'O'), (u'JUGGLING', u'O'), (u'PARENTHOOD,', u'O'), (u'ALWAYS', u'O'), (u'FINDING', u'O'), (u'TIME', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'CHILDREN.', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'TALENTED', u'O'), (u'PAINTER,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'ALSO', u'O'), (u'FOUND', u'O'), (u'TIME', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'STUDY', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'ARTS', u'O'), (u'STUDENTS', u'O'), (u'LEAGUE', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'NEW', u'LOCATION'), (u'YORK', u'LOCATION'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'REGINALD', u'PERSON'), (u'MARSH.', u'O'), (u'THEN,', u'O'), (u'WHEN', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'SONS', u'O'), (u'WENT', u'O'), (u'OFF', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'COLLEGE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'DAUGHTER', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'BIT', u'O'), (u'MORE', u'O'), (u'INDEPENDENT,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'TOOK', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'RESIDENCY', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'ANESTHESIOLOGY', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'ALBERT', u'PERSON'), (u'EINSTEIN', u'PERSON'), (u'COLLEGE', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'MEDICINE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'FOLLOWING,', u'O'), (u'CONTINUED', u'O'), (u'WORK', u'O'), (u'FULL', u'O'), (u'TIME', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'AN', u'O'), (u'ATTENDING', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ASSOCIATE', u'O'), (u'PROFESSOR', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'ALBERT', u'PERSON'), (u'EINSTEIN', u'PERSON'), (u'COLLEGE', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'MEDICINE.', u'O'), (u'THERE,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'CREATED', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'PEDIATRIC', u'O'), (u'ANESTHESIA', u'O'), (u'SPECIALTY', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'BECAME', u'O'), (u'ASSISTANT', u'O'), (u'PROFESSOR', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'PEDIATRICS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'CLINICAL', u'O'), (u'DIRECTOR', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'DEPARTMENT', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'ANESTHESIA.', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'PERFECTLY', u'O'), (u'SUITED', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'PEDIATRICS,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'LOVED', u'O'), (u'CHILDREN,', u'O'), (u'WOULD', u'O'), (u'COMPASSIONATELY', u'O'), (u'READY', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'YOUNG', u'O'), (u'PATIENTS', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'SURGERY,', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'COMFORTINGLY', u'O'), (u'ALLAY', u'O'), (u'THEIR', u'O'), (u'FEARS.', u'O'), (u'RETURNING', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'LATER', u'O'), (u'YEARS', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'CORE', u'O'), (u'DESIRE', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'HELP', u'O'), (u'THOSE', u'O'), (u'WITHOUT', u'O'), (u'RESOURCES,', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'BRODMAN', u'PERSON'), (u'VOLUNTEERED', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'HUSBAND', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'WORK', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THIRD', u'O'), (u'WORLD', u'O'), (u'COUNTRIES,', u'O'), (u'GIVING', u'O'), (u'ANESTHESIA', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'NEEDY', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'TEACHING', u'O'), (u'FOREIGN', u'O'), (u'PHYSICIANS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THEIR', u'O'), (u'OWN', u'O'), (u'LANDS,', u'O'), (u'USING', u'O'), (u'MATERIALS', u'O'), (u'AVAILABLE', u'O'), (u'THERE', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'TEACH', u'O'), (u'NEW', u'O'), (u'TECHNIQUES.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1972', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'WORKED', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'AVICENNA', u'O'), (u'HOSPITAL', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'KABUL,', u'O'), (u'AFGHANISTAN;', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1975', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'SURAKARTA', u'LOCATION'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'MALANG,', u'O'), (u'JAVA;', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1991', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'HANGCHOU,', u'O'), (u'CHINA', u'LOCATION'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1992', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'LUTHERAN', u'O'), (u'HOSPITAL', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'WEST', u'O'), (u'BANK', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'ISRAEL.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'AFGHANISTAN', u'LOCATION'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'BRODMAN', u'PERSON'), (u'EXECUTED', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'TAUGHT', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'CENTRAL', u'O'), (u'VENOUS', u'O'), (u'MONITORING', u'O'), (u'TECHNIQUE,', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'FIRST', u'O'), (u'SUCH', u'O'), (u'PROCEDURE', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'CENTRAL', u'O'), (u'ASIA.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'CHINA', u'LOCATION'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ISRAEL', u'LOCATION'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'ESPECIALLY', u'O'), (u'FOND', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'WORK,', u'O'), (u'CORRECTING', u'O'), (u'FACIAL', u'O'), (u'DEFORMITIES', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'CHILDREN', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'GIVE', u'O'), (u'THEM', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'NEW', u'O'), (u'CHANCE', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'LIFE.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1995', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'50TH', u'O'), (u'MEDICAL', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL', u'O'), (u'REUNION,', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'BRODMAN', u'PERSON'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'GIVEN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'DISTINGUISHED', u'O'), (u'ALUMNI', u'O'), (u'AWARD', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'CLASS', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'1945.', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'BRODMAN', u'PERSON'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'RESPECTED', u'O'), (u'MEMBER', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'AMERICAN', u'O'), (u'SOCIETY', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'ANESTHESIOLOGISTS,', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'NEW', u'LOCATION'), (u'YORK', u'LOCATION'), (u'STATE', u'O'), (u'SOCIETY', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'ANESTHESIOLOGISTS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'INTERNATIONAL', u'O'), (u'ANESTHESIA', u'O'), (u'RESEARCH', u'O'), (u'SOCIETY.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'ADDITION,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'AUTHORED', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'CO,', u'O'), (u'AUTHORED', u'O'), (u'NUMEROUS', u'O'), (u'COMMUNICATIONS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'REVIEWED', u'O'), (u'JOURNALS', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'WELL', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'SEVERAL', u'O'), (u'BOOKS,', u'O'), (u'BOOK', u'O'), (u'CHAPTERS,', u'O'), (u'REVIEW', u'O'), (u'ARTICLES', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ABSTRACTS.', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'BRODMAN', u'PERSON'), (u'RETIRED', u'O'), (u'FROM', u'O'), (u'MEDICINE', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'AGE', u'O'), (u'76,', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'SAID,', u'O'), (u'""BEFORE', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'MADE', u'O'), (u'ANY', u'O'), (u'MISTAKES.""', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'WOULD', u'O'), (u'HAVE', u'O'), (u'LIKED', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'HAVE', u'O'), (u'DIED', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'BOOTS', u'O'), (u'ON,', u'O'), (u'PRACTICING', u'O'), (u'MEDICINE.', u'O'), (u'NEVER', u'O'), (u'LIKING', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'BE', u'O'), (u'INACTIVE,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'RETURNED', u'O'), (u'AFTER', u'O'), (u'RETIRING', u'O'), (u'FROM', u'O'), (u'MEDICINE', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'STUDYING', u'O'), (u'PAINTING', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'ARTS', u'O'), (u'STUDENTS', u'O'), (u'LEAGUE', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'VYTLACIL', u'O'), (u'CAMPUS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'SPARKILL,', u'O'), (u'NY.', u'O'), (u'ALWAYS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'DEEP', u'O'), (u'SORROW,', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'PREDECEASED', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'SON', u'O'), (u'CHARLES', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1977', u'O'), (u'WHEN', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'31,', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'HEART', u'O'), (u'BREAKING', u'O'), (u'LOSS', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'FAMILY', u'O'), (u'WHICH', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'HELD', u'O'), (u'TOGETHER', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'NOTHING', u'O'), (u'SHORT', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'GRACE,', u'O'), (u'LOVE,', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'ASTONISHING', u'O'), (u'STRENGTH', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'WILL.', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'YEAR', u'O'), (u'LATER,', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'O'), (u'SUFFERED', u'O'), (u'ANOTHER', u'O'), (u'TERRIBLE', u'O'), (u'LOSS,', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'GREATEST', u'O'), (u'CONFIDANT', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'FRIEND,', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'SISTER', u'O'), (u'MIDGE,', u'O'), (u'DIED', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'CAR', u'O'), (u'ACCIDENT.', u'O'), (u'AGAIN', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'O'), (u'DID', u'O'), (u'NOT', u'O'), (u'LET', u'O'), (u'LOSS,', u'O'), (u'THOUGH', u'O'), (u'EVER', u'O'), (u'PRESENT,', u'O'), (u'DEFINE', u'O'), (u'HER;', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'QUIETLY,', u'O'), (u'COMPASSIONATELY,', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'LOVINGLY', u'O'), (u'PERSEVERED.', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'B.', u'PERSON'), (u'BRODMAN', u'PERSON'), (u'IS', u'O'), (u'SURVIVED', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'DEVOTED', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ADORING', u'O'), (u'FAMILY:', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'HUSBAND', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'ALMOST', u'O'), (u'72', u'O'), (u'YEARS,', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'HAROLD', u'PERSON'), (u'BRODMAN,', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'GENERAL', u'O'), (u'SURGEON,', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'SON', u'O'), (u'DR.', u'O'), (u'RICHARD', u'O'), (u'BRODMAN,', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'CARDIOTHORACIC', u'O'), (u'SURGEON,', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'DAUGHTER,', u'O'), (u'LOUISE,', u'O'), (u'AN', u'O'), (u'ARCHITECT,', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'GRANDDAUGHTER,', u'O'), (u'ALEXANDRA,', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'NASSAU', u'O'), (u'COUNTY', u'O'), (u'ASSISTANT', u'O'), (u'DISTRICT', u'O'), (u'ATTORNEY,', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'THEIR', u'O'), (u'SPOUSES,', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'WELL', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'HERO', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'HARLEY,', u'O'), (u'POODLES', u'O'), (u'WHO', u'O'), (u'BROUGHT', u'O'), (u'SOME', u'O'), (u'LIGHT', u'O'), (u'HEARTED', u'O'), (u'PLAY', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'LAST', u'O'), (u'YEARS.', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'MOST', u'O'), (u'GENEROUS', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'SOULS,', u'O'), (u'AN', u'O'), (u'ENVIRONMENTALIST', u'O'), (u'BEFORE', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'WORD', u'O'), (u'BECAME', u'O'), (u'KNOWN,', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'COURAGEOUS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'FUN', u'O'), (u'LOVING', u'O'), (u'ADVENTURER', u'O'), (u'WHO', u'O'), (u'CANOED', u'O'), (u'WHITE', u'O'), (u'WATER', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'TRAVELED', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'WORLD', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'DESIRE', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'HELP', u'O'), (u'OTHERS,', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'PAINTER', u'O'), (u'WHO', u'O'), (u'LOVED', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'BEAUTY', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'NATURAL', u'O'), (u'WORLD', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'WELL', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'WONDERS', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'SCIENTISTS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ARTISTS,', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'LOVING', u'O'), (u'MOTHER', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'SPOUSE,', u'O'), (u'ELIZABETH', u'PERSON'), (u'MADE', u'O'), (u'EVERYONE', u'O'), (u'BETTER', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'HAVING', u'O'), (u'KNOWN', u'O'), (u'HER.', u'O'), (u'DESPITE', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'SORROWS', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'SUFFERED', u'O'), (u'OVER', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'REMARKABLE', u'O'), (u'LIFE,', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'MADE', u'O'), (u'EVERYTHING', u'O'), (u'SEEM', u'O'), (u'EFFORTLESS,', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'JOYFUL.', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'LIVED', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'HER', u'O'), (u'OWN', u'O'), (u'EXPECTATIONS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'INTERESTS.', u'O'), (u'SHE', u'O'), (u'LOVED', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'LOVED.', u'O'), (u'1', u'O')]]"
"[""Republican Bush Says Rival Rubio Has 'Given Up'"", [(u'Republican', u'O'), (u'Bush', u'PERSON'), (u'Says', u'O'), (u'Rival', u'O'), (u'Rubio', u'O'), (u'Has', u'O'), (u""'Given"", u'O'), (u""Up'"", u'O')]]"
"['Market Slides on Concerns of Cooling Global Economy', [(u'Market', u'O'), (u'Slides', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Concerns', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Cooling', u'O'), (u'Global', u'O'), (u'Economy', u'O')]]"
"['Germany vs. Netherlands Friendly to Symbolize Unity: Loew', [(u'Germany', u'LOCATION'), (u'vs.', u'O'), (u'Netherlands', u'O'), (u'Friendly', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Symbolize', u'O'), (u'Unity:', u'O'), (u'Loew', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['The Limits of the \xe2\x80\x98Tobacco Strategy\xe2\x80\x99 on Climate Change', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Limits', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'‘Tobacco', u'O'), (u'Strategy’', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Climate', u'O'), (u'Change', u'O')]]"
"['Mark Penn\xe2\x80\x99s Stagwell Group Will Acquire SKDKnickerbocker', [(u'Mark', u'O'), (u'Penn’s', u'O'), (u'Stagwell', u'O'), (u'Group', u'O'), (u'Will', u'O'), (u'Acquire', u'O'), (u'SKDKnickerbocker', u'O')]]"
"['Rosberg Fastest in Final Mexican Practice', [(u'Rosberg', u'PERSON'), (u'Fastest', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Final', u'O'), (u'Mexican', u'O'), (u'Practice', u'O')]]"
"['German Industry Orders Unexpectedly Fall in August', [(u'German', u'O'), (u'Industry', u'O'), (u'Orders', u'O'), (u'Unexpectedly', u'O'), (u'Fall', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'August', u'O')]]"
"['Review: &#8216;Breathe,&#8217; the Story of a Scary Teenage Romance', [(u'Review:', u'O'), (u'&#8216;Breathe,&#8217;', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Story', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Scary', u'O'), (u'Teenage', u'O'), (u'Romance', u'O')]]"
"['North Korea to Hold Convention for Workers\xe2\x80\x99 Party', [(u'North', u'LOCATION'), (u'Korea', u'LOCATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Hold', u'O'), (u'Convention', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Workers’', u'O'), (u'Party', u'O')]]"
"['Charleston Voters Choose First New Mayor in Four Decades', [(u'Charleston', u'LOCATION'), (u'Voters', u'O'), (u'Choose', u'O'), (u'First', u'O'), (u'New', u'O'), (u'Mayor', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Four', u'O'), (u'Decades', u'O')]]"
"['How Drunk? Estimates Questioned in Drunken-Driving Cases', [(u'How', u'O'), (u'Drunk?', u'O'), (u'Estimates', u'O'), (u'Questioned', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Drunken-Driving', u'O'), (u'Cases', u'O')]]"
"['Samantha Bee to Be Among Guests at BookCon in 2016', [(u'Samantha', u'PERSON'), (u'Bee', u'PERSON'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Be', u'O'), (u'Among', u'O'), (u'Guests', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'BookCon', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'2016', u'O')]]"
"['Two Finals Entail Two Surfaces for Andy Murray', [(u'Two', u'O'), (u'Finals', u'O'), (u'Entail', u'O'), (u'Two', u'O'), (u'Surfaces', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Andy', u'PERSON'), (u'Murray', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Ban Ki-moon Urges Paris Climate Deal', [(u'Ban', u'O'), (u'Ki-moon', u'O'), (u'Urges', u'O'), (u'Paris', u'O'), (u'Climate', u'O'), (u'Deal', u'O')]]"
"['3 Startups That Want to Get Millennials Saving Money', [(u'3', u'O'), (u'Startups', u'O'), (u'That', u'O'), (u'Want', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Get', u'O'), (u'Millennials', u'O'), (u'Saving', u'O'), (u'Money', u'O')]]"
"['Detroit Symphony Tackles an Adventurous Premiere', [(u'Detroit', u'O'), (u'Symphony', u'O'), (u'Tackles', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'Adventurous', u'O'), (u'Premiere', u'O')]]"
"['VW Reveals It Misstated Emissions of Gas Cars', [(u'VW', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Reveals', u'O'), (u'It', u'O'), (u'Misstated', u'O'), (u'Emissions', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Gas', u'O'), (u'Cars', u'O')]]"
"['Travel News: BYO Crockpot; Cocktail Conference; 1-Year Tour', [(u'Travel', u'O'), (u'News:', u'O'), (u'BYO', u'O'), (u'Crockpot;', u'O'), (u'Cocktail', u'O'), (u'Conference;', u'O'), (u'1-Year', u'O'), (u'Tour', u'O')]]"
"['US Reaches $95.5M Settlement in For-Profit Education Case', [(u'US', u'LOCATION'), (u'Reaches', u'O'), (u'$95.5M', u'O'), (u'Settlement', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'For-Profit', u'O'), (u'Education', u'O'), (u'Case', u'O')]]"
"['Lindsey Graham to Make His Voice Heard During Debate, on Social Media', [(u'Lindsey', u'PERSON'), (u'Graham', u'PERSON'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Make', u'O'), (u'His', u'O'), (u'Voice', u'O'), (u'Heard', u'O'), (u'During', u'O'), (u'Debate,', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Social', u'O'), (u'Media', u'O')]]"
"['Trial for Church Shooting Suspect Friend Moved to Charleston', [(u'Trial', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Church', u'O'), (u'Shooting', u'O'), (u'Suspect', u'O'), (u'Friend', u'O'), (u'Moved', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Charleston', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['With \xe2\x80\x98Product,\xe2\x80\x99 Sophie Swarms the Senses With Synthetic Sounds', [(u'With', u'O'), (u'‘Product,’', u'O'), (u'Sophie', u'PERSON'), (u'Swarms', u'PERSON'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Senses', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Synthetic', u'O'), (u'Sounds', u'O')]]"
"['Loss to Penn Ends Streak of 22 Wins for Harvard', [(u'Loss', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Penn', u'PERSON'), (u'Ends', u'PERSON'), (u'Streak', u'PERSON'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'22', u'O'), (u'Wins', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Harvard', u'O')]]"
"[""Paris gunmen 'no older than 25': survivor"", [(u'Paris', u'LOCATION'), (u'gunmen', u'O'), (u""'no"", u'O'), (u'older', u'O'), (u'than', u'O'), (u""25':"", u'O'), (u'survivor', u'O')]]"
"['At Home \xe2\x80\x94 and on the Hunt for Antiques \xe2\x80\x94 With Heidi Julavits', [(u'At', u'O'), (u'Home', u'O'), (u'—', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Hunt', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Antiques', u'O'), (u'—', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Heidi', u'PERSON'), (u'Julavits', u'PERSON')]]"
"[""Breeders' Cup Classic Winners"", [(u""Breeders'"", u'O'), (u'Cup', u'O'), (u'Classic', u'O'), (u'Winners', u'O')]]"
"['Consumer Spending Posts Smallest Gain in 8 Months', [(u'Consumer', u'O'), (u'Spending', u'O'), (u'Posts', u'O'), (u'Smallest', u'O'), (u'Gain', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'8', u'O'), (u'Months', u'O')]]"
"['James Prideaux, Writer for Stage and for Television, Dies at 88', [(u'James', u'PERSON'), (u'Prideaux,', u'O'), (u'Writer', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Stage', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Television,', u'O'), (u'Dies', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'88', u'O')]]"
"[""Real's Bale Fit and Ready for 'Clasico' Battle"", [(u""Real's"", u'O'), (u'Bale', u'O'), (u'Fit', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Ready', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u""'Clasico'"", u'O'), (u'Battle', u'O')]]"
"['The Third Trail', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Third', u'O'), (u'Trail', u'O')]]"
"[""'Say Something' Slogan, Born of Terror, Adopted for Schools"", [(u""'Say"", u'O'), (u""Something'"", u'O'), (u'Slogan,', u'O'), (u'Born', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Terror,', u'O'), (u'Adopted', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Schools', u'O')]]"
"['3 of a Kind: Rare Identical Triplets Born in Baltimore', [(u'3', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Kind:', u'O'), (u'Rare', u'O'), (u'Identical', u'O'), (u'Triplets', u'O'), (u'Born', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Baltimore', u'LOCATION')]]"
"[""High Speed, Mountains Blunt Hurricane Patricia's Blow in Mexico"", [(u'High', u'O'), (u'Speed,', u'O'), (u'Mountains', u'O'), (u'Blunt', u'O'), (u'Hurricane', u'O'), (u""Patricia's"", u'O'), (u'Blow', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Mexico', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['They\xe2\x80\x99re Coming for Your Cigarettes. But That\xe2\x80\x99s O.K.', [(u'They’re', u'O'), (u'Coming', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Your', u'O'), (u'Cigarettes.', u'O'), (u'But', u'O'), (u'That’s', u'O'), (u'O.K.', u'O')]]"
"['Endangered White Rhino Dies at San Diego-Area Zoo', [(u'Endangered', u'O'), (u'White', u'O'), (u'Rhino', u'O'), (u'Dies', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'San', u'LOCATION'), (u'Diego-Area', u'LOCATION'), (u'Zoo', u'LOCATION')]]"
"[""Leicester's Vardy Has Van Nistelrooy Record in Sight"", [(u""Leicester's"", u'O'), (u'Vardy', u'PERSON'), (u'Has', u'PERSON'), (u'Van', u'PERSON'), (u'Nistelrooy', u'PERSON'), (u'Record', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Sight', u'O')]]"
"['Busta Rhymes Sentenced to Time Served in Protein Shake Incident', [(u'Busta', u'O'), (u'Rhymes', u'O'), (u'Sentenced', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Time', u'O'), (u'Served', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Protein', u'O'), (u'Shake', u'O'), (u'Incident', u'O')]]"
"['Record Setting Quarter for Aerospace and Defence M&A-Report', [(u'Record', u'O'), (u'Setting', u'O'), (u'Quarter', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Aerospace', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Defence', u'O'), (u'M&A-Report', u'O')]]"
"['Panel: Cooking With The Times', [(u'Panel:', u'O'), (u'Cooking', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Times', u'O')]]"
"['In This  Festival, All the Films Are Dogs', [(u'In', u'O'), (u'This', u'O'), (u'Festival,', u'O'), (u'All', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Films', u'O'), (u'Are', u'O'), (u'Dogs', u'O')]]"
"['Match Shares Gain on Their Debut', [(u'Match', u'O'), (u'Shares', u'O'), (u'Gain', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Their', u'O'), (u'Debut', u'O')]]"
"[""BHP Billiton Says Keeping Solid 'A' Balance Sheet Is Top Priority"", [(u'BHP', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Billiton', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Says', u'O'), (u'Keeping', u'O'), (u'Solid', u'O'), (u""'A'"", u'O'), (u'Balance', u'O'), (u'Sheet', u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'Top', u'O'), (u'Priority', u'O')]]"
"[""The Clockmakers' Museum: Keeping Time"", [(u'The', u'O'), (u""Clockmakers'"", u'O'), (u'Museum:', u'O'), (u'Keeping', u'O'), (u'Time', u'O')]]"
"['Fecal Transplants Made (Somewhat) More Palatable', [(u'Fecal', u'O'), (u'Transplants', u'O'), (u'Made', u'O'), (u'(Somewhat)', u'O'), (u'More', u'O'), (u'Palatable', u'O')]]"
"['Analysis-Other Central Banks Set to Act, but Swiss Policy Cupboard Bare', [(u'Analysis-Other', u'O'), (u'Central', u'O'), (u'Banks', u'O'), (u'Set', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Act,', u'O'), (u'but', u'O'), (u'Swiss', u'O'), (u'Policy', u'O'), (u'Cupboard', u'O'), (u'Bare', u'O')]]"
"['The Showcase That Sets a Home Apart From Others', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Showcase', u'O'), (u'That', u'O'), (u'Sets', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Home', u'O'), (u'Apart', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'Others', u'O')]]"
"['Paris and London, in Their Annual Art Showdown', [(u'Paris', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'London,', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Their', u'O'), (u'Annual', u'O'), (u'Art', u'O'), (u'Showdown', u'O')]]"
"[""New York Assembly Speaker's Conviction Renews Call to Ban Outside Income"", [(u'New', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'York', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Assembly', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u""Speaker's"", u'O'), (u'Conviction', u'O'), (u'Renews', u'O'), (u'Call', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Ban', u'O'), (u'Outside', u'O'), (u'Income', u'O')]]"
"['Whistleblower Letter Backs Lloyds Investor Claims Over HBOS Purchase-Lawyers', [(u'Whistleblower', u'O'), (u'Letter', u'O'), (u'Backs', u'O'), (u'Lloyds', u'O'), (u'Investor', u'O'), (u'Claims', u'O'), (u'Over', u'O'), (u'HBOS', u'O'), (u'Purchase-Lawyers', u'O')]]"
"['Rosberg Blames Gust of Wind for Austin Error', [(u'Rosberg', u'PERSON'), (u'Blames', u'O'), (u'Gust', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Wind', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Austin', u'O'), (u'Error', u'O')]]"
"['Friday Night Music: The Lone Bellow Cover The Rolling Stones', [(u'Friday', u'O'), (u'Night', u'O'), (u'Music:', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Lone', u'O'), (u'Bellow', u'O'), (u'Cover', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Rolling', u'O'), (u'Stones', u'O')]]"
"['U.S. Investors Interested in Buying Marussia', [(u'U.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Investors', u'O'), (u'Interested', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Buying', u'O'), (u'Marussia', u'O')]]"
"['Ukraine Leaves Sabotaged Power Lines to Russian-Annexed Crimea in Mud', [(u'Ukraine', u'LOCATION'), (u'Leaves', u'O'), (u'Sabotaged', u'O'), (u'Power', u'O'), (u'Lines', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Russian-Annexed', u'O'), (u'Crimea', u'LOCATION'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Mud', u'O')]]"
"[""'Mad Max: Fury Road' Is Surprise Best Film Choice of Board of Review"", [(u""'Mad"", u'O'), (u'Max:', u'O'), (u'Fury', u'O'), (u""Road'"", u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'Surprise', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Best', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Film', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Choice', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'of', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Board', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'of', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Review', u'ORGANIZATION')]]"
"['Leftist Alliance Moves Closer to Power in Portugal', [(u'Leftist', u'O'), (u'Alliance', u'O'), (u'Moves', u'O'), (u'Closer', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Power', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Portugal', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['The California Wildfires: What\xe2\x80\x99s Making This Season So Wild?', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'California', u'LOCATION'), (u'Wildfires:', u'O'), (u'What’s', u'O'), (u'Making', u'O'), (u'This', u'O'), (u'Season', u'O'), (u'So', u'O'), (u'Wild?', u'O')]]"
"['John Doyle to Be Artistic Director of the Classic Stage Company', [(u'John', u'PERSON'), (u'Doyle', u'PERSON'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Be', u'O'), (u'Artistic', u'O'), (u'Director', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Classic', u'O'), (u'Stage', u'O'), (u'Company', u'O')]]"
"['Paid Notice: Deaths  LEEDS, HERBERT ALAN DIED PEACEFULLY OCTOBER 5', [(u'Paid', u'O'), (u'Notice:', u'O'), (u'Deaths', u'O'), (u'LEEDS,', u'O'), (u'HERBERT', u'PERSON'), (u'ALAN', u'PERSON'), (u'DIED', u'O'), (u'PEACEFULLY', u'O'), (u'OCTOBER', u'O'), (u'5', u'O')]]"
"['One Bourbon, One Scotch, One Meal', [(u'One', u'O'), (u'Bourbon,', u'O'), (u'One', u'O'), (u'Scotch,', u'O'), (u'One', u'O'), (u'Meal', u'O')]]"
"['Brad Pitt, Ryan Gosling and Other Stars at \xe2\x80\x98The Big Short\xe2\x80\x99 Premiere', [(u'Brad', u'PERSON'), (u'Pitt,', u'PERSON'), (u'Ryan', u'PERSON'), (u'Gosling', u'PERSON'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Other', u'O'), (u'Stars', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'‘The', u'O'), (u'Big', u'O'), (u'Short’', u'O'), (u'Premiere', u'O')]]"
"['Test of Will and Patience Follows Days of Preparation for Hillary Clinton', [(u'Test', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Will', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Patience', u'O'), (u'Follows', u'O'), (u'Days', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Preparation', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Hillary', u'PERSON'), (u'Clinton', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Beyond Monticello and Mount Vernon: The Other Presidents\xe2\x80\x99 Houses', [(u'Beyond', u'O'), (u'Monticello', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Mount', u'O'), (u'Vernon:', u'O'), (u'The', u'O'), (u'Other', u'O'), (u'Presidents’', u'O'), (u'Houses', u'O')]]"
"['Lancashire Shares Hit Record High on Special Dividend', [(u'Lancashire', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Shares', u'O'), (u'Hit', u'O'), (u'Record', u'O'), (u'High', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Special', u'O'), (u'Dividend', u'O')]]"
"['Exxon Taps High-Profile Lawyer to Fight N.Y. Climate Change Probe', [(u'Exxon', u'O'), (u'Taps', u'O'), (u'High-Profile', u'O'), (u'Lawyer', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Fight', u'O'), (u'N.Y.', u'O'), (u'Climate', u'O'), (u'Change', u'O'), (u'Probe', u'O')]]"
"['Texas Mother Teaches Textbook Company a Lesson on Accuracy', [(u'Texas', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Mother', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Teaches', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Textbook', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Company', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Lesson', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Accuracy', u'O')]]"
"['A Show of Appreciation at U.C.L.A.', [(u'A', u'O'), (u'Show', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Appreciation', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'U.C.L.A.', u'O')]]"
"['EasyJet Expects Resilient Demand to Withstand Security Fears', [(u'EasyJet', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Expects', u'O'), (u'Resilient', u'O'), (u'Demand', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Withstand', u'O'), (u'Security', u'O'), (u'Fears', u'O')]]"
"[""Prosecutor: Cause of 3-Year-Old Boy's Death Undetermined"", [(u'Prosecutor:', u'O'), (u'Cause', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'3-Year-Old', u'O'), (u""Boy's"", u'O'), (u'Death', u'O'), (u'Undetermined', u'O')]]"
"['Running Away With the Circus', [(u'Running', u'O'), (u'Away', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Circus', u'O')]]"
"['Fiji Intend to Finish With a Flourish', [(u'Fiji', u'LOCATION'), (u'Intend', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Finish', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Flourish', u'O')]]"
"['Almost Missing Summer', [(u'Almost', u'O'), (u'Missing', u'O'), (u'Summer', u'O')]]"
"['Advice on Lending to Adult Children', [(u'Advice', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Lending', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Adult', u'O'), (u'Children', u'O')]]"
"['U.S. Clears Genetically Modified Salmon for Human Consumption', [(u'U.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'Clears', u'O'), (u'Genetically', u'O'), (u'Modified', u'O'), (u'Salmon', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Human', u'O'), (u'Consumption', u'O')]]"
"['Virtual Tour of Off-Limits Ellis Island Site Now Available', [(u'Virtual', u'O'), (u'Tour', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Off-Limits', u'O'), (u'Ellis', u'PERSON'), (u'Island', u'O'), (u'Site', u'O'), (u'Now', u'O'), (u'Available', u'O')]]"
"['Spanish Woman Arrested for IS Group Links', [(u'Spanish', u'O'), (u'Woman', u'O'), (u'Arrested', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'IS', u'O'), (u'Group', u'O'), (u'Links', u'O')]]"
"['Hungary Waits on Austria, Germany Before Sealing Off Croatian Border', [(u'Hungary', u'LOCATION'), (u'Waits', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Austria,', u'O'), (u'Germany', u'LOCATION'), (u'Before', u'O'), (u'Sealing', u'O'), (u'Off', u'O'), (u'Croatian', u'O'), (u'Border', u'O')]]"
"['Fire in Coal Mine Kills at Least 21 in China', [(u'Fire', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Coal', u'O'), (u'Mine', u'O'), (u'Kills', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Least', u'O'), (u'21', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'China', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Bronx Baby Thrown Out Window Dies; Mother Is Charged With Murder', [(u'Bronx', u'O'), (u'Baby', u'O'), (u'Thrown', u'O'), (u'Out', u'O'), (u'Window', u'O'), (u'Dies;', u'O'), (u'Mother', u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'Charged', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Murder', u'O')]]"
"[""'Brexit' Wouldn't Ruin Northern Ireland Economy-Leadership Favorite"", [(u""'Brexit'"", u'O'), (u""Wouldn't"", u'O'), (u'Ruin', u'O'), (u'Northern', u'O'), (u'Ireland', u'O'), (u'Economy-Leadership', u'O'), (u'Favorite', u'O')]]"
"['Greek Fortress, Key to Ancient Jerusalem, Uncovered, Researchers Say', [(u'Greek', u'O'), (u'Fortress,', u'O'), (u'Key', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Ancient', u'O'), (u'Jerusalem,', u'O'), (u'Uncovered,', u'O'), (u'Researchers', u'O'), (u'Say', u'O')]]"
"['Jeb Bush Says He Would Have Probably Skipped Climate Conference', [(u'Jeb', u'PERSON'), (u'Bush', u'PERSON'), (u'Says', u'O'), (u'He', u'O'), (u'Would', u'O'), (u'Have', u'O'), (u'Probably', u'O'), (u'Skipped', u'O'), (u'Climate', u'O'), (u'Conference', u'O')]]"
"['John Thain of CIT Group Will Step Down as Chief Executive', [(u'John', u'PERSON'), (u'Thain', u'PERSON'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'CIT', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Group', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Will', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Step', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Down', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Chief', u'O'), (u'Executive', u'O')]]"
"['NATO Invites Montenegro to Join, as Russia Plots Response', [(u'NATO', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Invites', u'O'), (u'Montenegro', u'LOCATION'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Join,', u'O'), (u'as', u'O'), (u'Russia', u'LOCATION'), (u'Plots', u'O'), (u'Response', u'O')]]"
"[""Christie's to Auction Margaret Thatcher's Clothes, Handbags"", [(u""Christie's"", u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Auction', u'O'), (u'Margaret', u'PERSON'), (u""Thatcher's"", u'O'), (u'Clothes,', u'O'), (u'Handbags', u'O')]]"
"['Airlines Reroute Flights After Russian Crash in Egypt', [(u'Airlines', u'O'), (u'Reroute', u'O'), (u'Flights', u'O'), (u'After', u'O'), (u'Russian', u'O'), (u'Crash', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Egypt', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Punish Russian Officials, Not Athletes for Doping-Shobukhova', [(u'Punish', u'O'), (u'Russian', u'O'), (u'Officials,', u'O'), (u'Not', u'O'), (u'Athletes', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Doping-Shobukhova', u'O')]]"
"['Paid Notice: Memorials  PARKER, H. LAWRENCE. RETIRED MANAGING DIRECTOR AT MORGAN STANLEY, DIES AT 89. AFTER A LENGTHY BATTLE WITH CANCER, H. LAWRENCE, ""LARRY,"" PARKER DIED PEACEFULLY ON OCTOBER 21ST, SURROUNDED BY FAMILY AT HIS HOME IN HOBE SOUND, FLORIDA. HE IS SURVIVED BY HIS WIFE, REGGIE HAWES PARKER, HIS DAUGHTER, KATHERINE GOLDSMITH, AND HIS TWO SONS, RICHARD AND MICHAEL. A SON, DOUGLAS, PREDECEASED LARRY IN 1976. HIS FAMILY ALSO INCLUDES SEVEN GRANDCHILDREN AND EIGHT GREAT, GRANDCHILDREN. HE IS ALSO SURVIVED BY HIS TWO SISTERS, NANCY WELBOURN AND ALICE OBER. BORN AND RAISED IN THE NORTHEASTERN U.S., HE ATTENDED ST. ANDREWS SCHOOL IN MIDDLETON, DELAWARE AND ENLISTED IN THE MARINE CORPS DAYS AFTER GRADUATION IN JUNE, 1944. ""PFC"" PARKER SERVED DURING WORLD WAR II ABOARD THE U.S.S. ATLANTA AND WAS AMONG THOSE PARTICIPATING IN THE FIRST LANDING OF AMERICAN TROOPS ON JAPAN IN LATE AUGUST, 1945. THE HONOR OF SERVING AS A MARINE WAS AS STRONG AT THE END OF HIS LIFE AS IT WAS IN 1944. LARRY GRADUATED FROM YALE UNIVERSITY, THEN IMMEDIATELY WENT TO WORK FOR MORGAN STANLEY & COMPANY IN 1950. RAPIDLY DISTINGUISHING HIMSELF FOR DILIGENCE AND FOR CULTIVATING TRUSTING AND CLOSE RELATIONSHIPS WITH CLIENTS, LARRY WAS THE YOUNGEST MAN TO BE MADE GENERAL PARTNER EVER IN 1959. OVER THE YEARS HE MANAGED KEY ACCOUNTS LIKE GMAC, THE WORLD BANK, AND WEYERHAEUSER AND ALSO SERVED AS CHAIRMAN OF MORGAN STANLEY CANADA LIMITED FROM 1979, 1983. HE ALSO SERVED A TERM AS PRESIDENT OF THE INVESTMENT BANKERS ASSOCIATION OF AMERICA, HIS NATIONAL ORGANIZATION, FROM 1969, 70. HE HAD A DISTINGUISHED CAREER AT MORGAN STANLEY AND RETIRED AS A MANAGING DIRECTOR IN 1983. DURING THESE YEARS, LARRY HOSTED HIS FAMILY FOR FOUR, SEASON ACTIVITY DURING VACATIONS IN STOWE, VERMONT. AFTER RETIREMENT LARRY DIVIDED HIS TIME BETWEEN CATTLE RANCHING IN DANIEL, WYOMING AND HIS LIFE IN HOBE SOUND. ALWAYS A LOVER OF HORSES AND THE MOUNTAINS, LARRY JOINED HIS NEIGHBORS IN FROSTY DAWN CATTLE DRIVES AND HAY CUTTING MARATHONS AND JOURNEYED INTO THE WIND RIVER RANGE WITH FRIENDS AND FAMILY ON PACK TRIPS AND ELK HUNTING EXCURSIONS. IN FLORIDA LARRY WAS VERY ACTIVE RAISING MONEY FOR THE JUPITER MEDICAL CENTER FOUNDATION AND WORKING AT KEY VOLUNTEER ROLES AT THE JUPITER ISLAND CLUB, MOST NOTABLY AS CHAIRMAN OF THE GOLF AND GREEN COMMITTEES. THROUGHOUT HIS LIFE, SERVICE TO OTHERS WAS IMPORTANT. HE ALSO SERVED AS COMMODORE OF THE HOBE SOUND YACHT CLUB AND WAS AN ACTIVE MEMBER IN THE UNITED STATES SENIORS\' GOLF ASSOCIATION. HE WAS A MEMBER AT AUGUSTA NATIONAL GOLF CLUB FOR OVER 40 YEARS AND SERVED ON THE ADMISSION COMMITTEE AND WAS CHAIRMAN OF THE COMMITTEE RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRODUCTION OF THE ANNUAL FILM OF THE MASTERS TOURNAMENT FOR OVER THREE DECADES. LARRY IS REMEMBERED BY FRIENDS AND FAMILY AS A TRUE GENTLEMAN. HIS GENEROSITY, KINDNESS, RESPECT FOR ALL, LOVE OF THE OUTDOORS, AND ZEST FOR LIFE INSPIRED THOSE WHO KNEW HIM. NOTHING WAS MORE IMPORTANT TO HIM THAN HIS FAMILY. LARRY PARKER, ""THE PARD"" A LIFE WELL LIVED. IN LIEU OF FLOWERS, PLEASE SEND DONATIONS IN LARRY\'S HONOR TO THE JUPITER MEDICAL CENTER FOUNDATION AT 1210 SOUTH OLD DIXIE HIGHWAY, BUILDING EAST 1002, JUPITER, FLORIDA 33458. A MEMORIAL SERVICE WILL BE HELD ON JUPITER ISLAND, JANUARY 23RD AT 4:30 AT CHRIST MEMORIAL CHAPEL. 1', [(u'Paid', u'O'), (u'Notice:', u'O'), (u'Memorials', u'O'), (u'PARKER,', u'O'), (u'H.', u'O'), (u'LAWRENCE.', u'O'), (u'RETIRED', u'O'), (u'MANAGING', u'O'), (u'DIRECTOR', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'MORGAN', u'LOCATION'), (u'STANLEY,', u'O'), (u'DIES', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'89.', u'O'), (u'AFTER', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'LENGTHY', u'O'), (u'BATTLE', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'CANCER,', u'O'), (u'H.', u'O'), (u'LAWRENCE,', u'O'), (u'""LARRY,""', u'O'), (u'PARKER', u'PERSON'), (u'DIED', u'O'), (u'PEACEFULLY', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'OCTOBER', u'O'), (u'21ST,', u'O'), (u'SURROUNDED', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'FAMILY', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'HOME', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'HOBE', u'O'), (u'SOUND,', u'O'), (u'FLORIDA.', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'IS', u'O'), (u'SURVIVED', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'WIFE,', u'O'), (u'REGGIE', u'PERSON'), (u'HAWES', u'PERSON'), (u'PARKER,', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'DAUGHTER,', u'O'), (u'KATHERINE', u'PERSON'), (u'GOLDSMITH,', u'PERSON'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'TWO', u'O'), (u'SONS,', u'O'), (u'RICHARD', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'MICHAEL.', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'SON,', u'O'), (u'DOUGLAS,', u'O'), (u'PREDECEASED', u'O'), (u'LARRY', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1976.', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'FAMILY', u'O'), (u'ALSO', u'O'), (u'INCLUDES', u'O'), (u'SEVEN', u'O'), (u'GRANDCHILDREN', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'EIGHT', u'O'), (u'GREAT,', u'O'), (u'GRANDCHILDREN.', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'IS', u'O'), (u'ALSO', u'O'), (u'SURVIVED', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'TWO', u'O'), (u'SISTERS,', u'O'), (u'NANCY', u'PERSON'), (u'WELBOURN', u'PERSON'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ALICE', u'PERSON'), (u'OBER.', u'O'), (u'BORN', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'RAISED', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'NORTHEASTERN', u'O'), (u'U.S.,', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'ATTENDED', u'O'), (u'ST.', u'O'), (u'ANDREWS', u'O'), (u'SCHOOL', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'MIDDLETON,', u'O'), (u'DELAWARE', u'LOCATION'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ENLISTED', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'MARINE', u'O'), (u'CORPS', u'O'), (u'DAYS', u'O'), (u'AFTER', u'O'), (u'GRADUATION', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'JUNE,', u'O'), (u'1944.', u'O'), (u'""PFC""', u'O'), (u'PARKER', u'PERSON'), (u'SERVED', u'O'), (u'DURING', u'O'), (u'WORLD', u'O'), (u'WAR', u'O'), (u'II', u'O'), (u'ABOARD', u'O'), (u'THE', u'LOCATION'), (u'U.S.S.', u'LOCATION'), (u'ATLANTA', u'LOCATION'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'AMONG', u'O'), (u'THOSE', u'O'), (u'PARTICIPATING', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'FIRST', u'O'), (u'LANDING', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'AMERICAN', u'O'), (u'TROOPS', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'JAPAN', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'LATE', u'O'), (u'AUGUST,', u'O'), (u'1945.', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'HONOR', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'SERVING', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'MARINE', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'STRONG', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'END', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'LIFE', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'IT', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1944.', u'O'), (u'LARRY', u'PERSON'), (u'GRADUATED', u'O'), (u'FROM', u'O'), (u'YALE', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'UNIVERSITY,', u'O'), (u'THEN', u'O'), (u'IMMEDIATELY', u'O'), (u'WENT', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'WORK', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'MORGAN', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'STANLEY', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'&', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'COMPANY', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1950.', u'O'), (u'RAPIDLY', u'O'), (u'DISTINGUISHING', u'O'), (u'HIMSELF', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'DILIGENCE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'CULTIVATING', u'O'), (u'TRUSTING', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'CLOSE', u'O'), (u'RELATIONSHIPS', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'CLIENTS,', u'O'), (u'LARRY', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'YOUNGEST', u'O'), (u'MAN', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'BE', u'O'), (u'MADE', u'O'), (u'GENERAL', u'O'), (u'PARTNER', u'O'), (u'EVER', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1959.', u'O'), (u'OVER', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'YEARS', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'MANAGED', u'O'), (u'KEY', u'O'), (u'ACCOUNTS', u'O'), (u'LIKE', u'O'), (u'GMAC,', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'WORLD', u'O'), (u'BANK,', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'WEYERHAEUSER', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ALSO', u'O'), (u'SERVED', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'CHAIRMAN', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'MORGAN', u'O'), (u'STANLEY', u'O'), (u'CANADA', u'LOCATION'), (u'LIMITED', u'O'), (u'FROM', u'O'), (u'1979,', u'O'), (u'1983.', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'ALSO', u'O'), (u'SERVED', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'TERM', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'PRESIDENT', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'INVESTMENT', u'O'), (u'BANKERS', u'O'), (u'ASSOCIATION', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'AMERICA,', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'NATIONAL', u'O'), (u'ORGANIZATION,', u'O'), (u'FROM', u'O'), (u'1969,', u'O'), (u'70.', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'HAD', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'DISTINGUISHED', u'O'), (u'CAREER', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'MORGAN', u'LOCATION'), (u'STANLEY', u'LOCATION'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'RETIRED', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'MANAGING', u'O'), (u'DIRECTOR', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'1983.', u'O'), (u'DURING', u'O'), (u'THESE', u'O'), (u'YEARS,', u'O'), (u'LARRY', u'O'), (u'HOSTED', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'FAMILY', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'FOUR,', u'O'), (u'SEASON', u'O'), (u'ACTIVITY', u'O'), (u'DURING', u'O'), (u'VACATIONS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'STOWE,', u'O'), (u'VERMONT.', u'O'), (u'AFTER', u'O'), (u'RETIREMENT', u'O'), (u'LARRY', u'O'), (u'DIVIDED', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'TIME', u'O'), (u'BETWEEN', u'O'), (u'CATTLE', u'O'), (u'RANCHING', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'DANIEL,', u'O'), (u'WYOMING', u'LOCATION'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'LIFE', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'HOBE', u'O'), (u'SOUND.', u'O'), (u'ALWAYS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'LOVER', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'HORSES', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'MOUNTAINS,', u'O'), (u'LARRY', u'O'), (u'JOINED', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'NEIGHBORS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'FROSTY', u'O'), (u'DAWN', u'O'), (u'CATTLE', u'O'), (u'DRIVES', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'HAY', u'O'), (u'CUTTING', u'O'), (u'MARATHONS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'JOURNEYED', u'O'), (u'INTO', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'WIND', u'O'), (u'RIVER', u'O'), (u'RANGE', u'O'), (u'WITH', u'O'), (u'FRIENDS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'FAMILY', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'PACK', u'O'), (u'TRIPS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ELK', u'O'), (u'HUNTING', u'O'), (u'EXCURSIONS.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'FLORIDA', u'LOCATION'), (u'LARRY', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'VERY', u'O'), (u'ACTIVE', u'O'), (u'RAISING', u'O'), (u'MONEY', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'JUPITER', u'O'), (u'MEDICAL', u'O'), (u'CENTER', u'O'), (u'FOUNDATION', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'WORKING', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'KEY', u'O'), (u'VOLUNTEER', u'O'), (u'ROLES', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'THE', u'LOCATION'), (u'JUPITER', u'LOCATION'), (u'ISLAND', u'LOCATION'), (u'CLUB,', u'O'), (u'MOST', u'O'), (u'NOTABLY', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'CHAIRMAN', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'GOLF', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'GREEN', u'O'), (u'COMMITTEES.', u'O'), (u'THROUGHOUT', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'LIFE,', u'O'), (u'SERVICE', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'OTHERS', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'IMPORTANT.', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'ALSO', u'O'), (u'SERVED', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'COMMODORE', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'HOBE', u'O'), (u'SOUND', u'O'), (u'YACHT', u'O'), (u'CLUB', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'AN', u'O'), (u'ACTIVE', u'O'), (u'MEMBER', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'UNITED', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'STATES', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u""SENIORS'"", u'O'), (u'GOLF', u'O'), (u'ASSOCIATION.', u'O'), (u'HE', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'MEMBER', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'AUGUSTA', u'LOCATION'), (u'NATIONAL', u'O'), (u'GOLF', u'O'), (u'CLUB', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'OVER', u'O'), (u'40', u'O'), (u'YEARS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'SERVED', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'ADMISSION', u'O'), (u'COMMITTEE', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'CHAIRMAN', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'COMMITTEE', u'O'), (u'RESPONSIBLE', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'PRODUCTION', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'ANNUAL', u'O'), (u'FILM', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'MASTERS', u'O'), (u'TOURNAMENT', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'OVER', u'O'), (u'THREE', u'O'), (u'DECADES.', u'O'), (u'LARRY', u'O'), (u'IS', u'O'), (u'REMEMBERED', u'O'), (u'BY', u'O'), (u'FRIENDS', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'FAMILY', u'O'), (u'AS', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'TRUE', u'O'), (u'GENTLEMAN.', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'GENEROSITY,', u'O'), (u'KINDNESS,', u'O'), (u'RESPECT', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'ALL,', u'O'), (u'LOVE', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'OUTDOORS,', u'O'), (u'AND', u'O'), (u'ZEST', u'O'), (u'FOR', u'O'), (u'LIFE', u'O'), (u'INSPIRED', u'O'), (u'THOSE', u'O'), (u'WHO', u'O'), (u'KNEW', u'O'), (u'HIM.', u'O'), (u'NOTHING', u'O'), (u'WAS', u'O'), (u'MORE', u'O'), (u'IMPORTANT', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'HIM', u'O'), (u'THAN', u'O'), (u'HIS', u'O'), (u'FAMILY.', u'O'), (u'LARRY', u'O'), (u'PARKER,', u'O'), (u'""THE', u'O'), (u'PARD""', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'LIFE', u'O'), (u'WELL', u'O'), (u'LIVED.', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u'LIEU', u'O'), (u'OF', u'O'), (u'FLOWERS,', u'O'), (u'PLEASE', u'O'), (u'SEND', u'O'), (u'DONATIONS', u'O'), (u'IN', u'O'), (u""LARRY'S"", u'O'), (u'HONOR', u'O'), (u'TO', u'O'), (u'THE', u'O'), (u'JUPITER', u'O'), (u'MEDICAL', u'O'), (u'CENTER', u'O'), (u'FOUNDATION', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'1210', u'O'), (u'SOUTH', u'O'), (u'OLD', u'O'), (u'DIXIE', u'O'), (u'HIGHWAY,', u'O'), (u'BUILDING', u'O'), (u'EAST', u'O'), (u'1002,', u'O'), (u'JUPITER,', u'O'), (u'FLORIDA', u'LOCATION'), (u'33458.', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'MEMORIAL', u'O'), (u'SERVICE', u'O'), (u'WILL', u'O'), (u'BE', u'O'), (u'HELD', u'O'), (u'ON', u'O'), (u'JUPITER', u'O'), (u'ISLAND,', u'O'), (u'JANUARY', u'O'), (u'23RD', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'4:30', u'O'), (u'AT', u'O'), (u'CHRIST', u'O'), (u'MEMORIAL', u'O'), (u'CHAPEL.', u'O'), (u'1', u'O')]]"
"['New Details in Akron Plane Crash', [(u'New', u'O'), (u'Details', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Akron', u'LOCATION'), (u'Plane', u'O'), (u'Crash', u'O')]]"
"['Bucs, Dolphins, Jags Already Falling Short of Expectations', [(u'Bucs,', u'O'), (u'Dolphins,', u'O'), (u'Jags', u'O'), (u'Already', u'O'), (u'Falling', u'O'), (u'Short', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Expectations', u'O')]]"
"['Tales of a Warmer Planet', [(u'Tales', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Warmer', u'O'), (u'Planet', u'O')]]"
"['Plants That Won\xe2\x80\x99t Drain You', [(u'Plants', u'O'), (u'That', u'O'), (u'Won’t', u'O'), (u'Drain', u'O'), (u'You', u'O')]]"
"['Travel New and Now: NYC Winter, DC Video Show, Lonely Planet', [(u'Travel', u'O'), (u'New', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Now:', u'O'), (u'NYC', u'O'), (u'Winter,', u'O'), (u'DC', u'O'), (u'Video', u'O'), (u'Show,', u'O'), (u'Lonely', u'O'), (u'Planet', u'O')]]"
"['Joseph Silverstein, Violinist and Boston Symphony Concertmaster, Dies at 83', [(u'Joseph', u'PERSON'), (u'Silverstein,', u'O'), (u'Violinist', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Boston', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Symphony', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Concertmaster,', u'O'), (u'Dies', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'83', u'O')]]"
"['$1,175,000 Homes in Hawaii, Colorado and Washington, D.C.', [(u'$1,175,000', u'O'), (u'Homes', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Hawaii,', u'O'), (u'Colorado', u'LOCATION'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Washington,', u'O'), (u'D.C.', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['Devils Owner Apologizes to Youths', [(u'Devils', u'O'), (u'Owner', u'O'), (u'Apologizes', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Youths', u'O')]]"
"['Is Carly Fiorina a Feminist?', [(u'Is', u'O'), (u'Carly', u'PERSON'), (u'Fiorina', u'PERSON'), (u'a', u'O'), (u'Feminist?', u'O')]]"
"['Nigerian Security Agencies Searching for Kidnapped Poles', [(u'Nigerian', u'O'), (u'Security', u'O'), (u'Agencies', u'O'), (u'Searching', u'O'), (u'for', u'O'), (u'Kidnapped', u'O'), (u'Poles', u'O')]]"
"['Why an Iowa Poll Is Unfair to Bernie Sanders', [(u'Why', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'Iowa', u'LOCATION'), (u'Poll', u'O'), (u'Is', u'O'), (u'Unfair', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Bernie', u'PERSON'), (u'Sanders', u'PERSON')]]"
"['Greece Improving Border Control, Cooperation-EU Chair', [(u'Greece', u'LOCATION'), (u'Improving', u'O'), (u'Border', u'O'), (u'Control,', u'O'), (u'Cooperation-EU', u'O'), (u'Chair', u'O')]]"
"['Tell Consumers What They Are Eating', [(u'Tell', u'O'), (u'Consumers', u'O'), (u'What', u'O'), (u'They', u'O'), (u'Are', u'O'), (u'Eating', u'O')]]"
"['Q &#038; A with Austin Meyer, 2015 Win-a-Trip Winner', [(u'Q', u'O'), (u'&#038;', u'O'), (u'A', u'O'), (u'with', u'O'), (u'Austin', u'PERSON'), (u'Meyer,', u'O'), (u'2015', u'O'), (u'Win-a-Trip', u'O'), (u'Winner', u'O')]]"
"['A Local Team Reflects Values and Culture of Employees and Customers', [(u'A', u'O'), (u'Local', u'O'), (u'Team', u'O'), (u'Reflects', u'O'), (u'Values', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Culture', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Employees', u'O'), (u'and', u'O'), (u'Customers', u'O')]]"
"['How the H-1B Visa System Can Hurt American Workers ', [(u'How', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'H-1B', u'O'), (u'Visa', u'O'), (u'System', u'O'), (u'Can', u'O'), (u'Hurt', u'O'), (u'American', u'O'), (u'Workers', u'O')]]"
"['Fetty Wap Throws Wads of Money Over Balcony to Fans at Mall', [(u'Fetty', u'O'), (u'Wap', u'O'), (u'Throws', u'O'), (u'Wads', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'Money', u'O'), (u'Over', u'O'), (u'Balcony', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Fans', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'Mall', u'O')]]"
"['A 3-Year-Old Syrian Refugee\xe2\x80\x99s Life Cut Short', [(u'A', u'O'), (u'3-Year-Old', u'O'), (u'Syrian', u'O'), (u'Refugee’s', u'O'), (u'Life', u'O'), (u'Cut', u'O'), (u'Short', u'O')]]"
"['Celtics Run Away From Wizards 111-78', [(u'Celtics', u'O'), (u'Run', u'O'), (u'Away', u'O'), (u'From', u'O'), (u'Wizards', u'O'), (u'111-78', u'O')]]"
"['Houston\xe2\x80\x99s Vote on an Anti-Bias Law', [(u'Houston’s', u'O'), (u'Vote', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'an', u'O'), (u'Anti-Bias', u'O'), (u'Law', u'O')]]"
"['Kim Birdies Last to Claim Stunning Victory in China', [(u'Kim', u'PERSON'), (u'Birdies', u'O'), (u'Last', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'Claim', u'O'), (u'Stunning', u'O'), (u'Victory', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'China', u'LOCATION')]]"
"[""South Africa's PIC Says All SABMiller Shareholders Be Treated Equally"", [(u'South', u'O'), (u""Africa's"", u'O'), (u'PIC', u'O'), (u'Says', u'O'), (u'All', u'O'), (u'SABMiller', u'O'), (u'Shareholders', u'O'), (u'Be', u'O'), (u'Treated', u'O'), (u'Equally', u'O')]]"
"['Man City Back on Top After Bore Draw, Klopp Still Awaiting Win', [(u'Man', u'O'), (u'City', u'O'), (u'Back', u'O'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'Top', u'O'), (u'After', u'O'), (u'Bore', u'O'), (u'Draw,', u'O'), (u'Klopp', u'O'), (u'Still', u'O'), (u'Awaiting', u'O'), (u'Win', u'O')]]"
"['U.N. Report Shows Women Inching Slowly, Unevenly Towards Equality', [(u'U.N.', u'ORGANIZATION'), (u'Report', u'O'), (u'Shows', u'O'), (u'Women', u'O'), (u'Inching', u'O'), (u'Slowly,', u'O'), (u'Unevenly', u'O'), (u'Towards', u'O'), (u'Equality', u'O')]]"
"['Acquittals Are Greeted With Good Cheer in Queens', [(u'Acquittals', u'O'), (u'Are', u'O'), (u'Greeted', u'O'), (u'With', u'O'), (u'Good', u'O'), (u'Cheer', u'O'), (u'in', u'O'), (u'Queens', u'LOCATION')]]"
"['The Week of the Woman', [(u'The', u'O'), (u'Week', u'O'), (u'of', u'O'), (u'the', u'O'), (u'Woman', u'O')]]"
"['A Mammoth Find', [(u'A', u'O'), (u'Mammoth', u'O'), (u'Find', u'O')]]"
"['Feting Alice, Forever Young at 150', [(u'Feting', u'O'), (u'Alice,', u'O'), (u'Forever', u'O'), (u'Young', u'O'), (u'at', u'O'), (u'150', u'O')]]"
"['Hillary Rodham Clinton on ISIS', [(u'Hillary', u'PERSON'), (u'Rodham', u'PERSON'), (u'Clinton', u'PERSON'), (u'on', u'O'), (u'ISIS', u'ORGANIZATION')]]"
"['US Rig Count Declines by 13 This Week to 744', [(u'US', u'LOCATION'), (u'Rig', u'O'), (u'Count', u'O'), (u'Declines', u'O'), (u'by', u'O'), (u'13', u'O'), (u'This', u'O'), (u'Week', u'O'), (u'to', u'O'), (u'744', u'O')]]"
